We have well, I just
I mean you guys and I know it looks like everybody like oh it looks like it's
It's like oh, it's like not it's not real. It's obviously not real. There's AI that like can like
Pick up on certain things and they will delete chill channels over over like form bombing
I mean just on the item. I'm not sure. That's why I asked
That was insane, right?
I mean, I mean, it's, you know, he has a nice, I mean, it's a nice size.
It's just like, it's not appropriate to show on my show.
Yeah, it didn't look, it looked really like a glance, you know.
It's like, I mean, his is probably a comparable size.
He has that like that confident look about him of like a you know, the the BDE
He's trying to give me bands the only things that I know what it's like see that's the second time
It's like he's like he's asked me
He where he's done other stuff like
That like he on Friday the 13th he was like showing like like the movie where they're like
Oh, there's all these like, you know violence and stuff. I'm afraid it's nothing. That's a lot look real
I know I don't talk about it was kind of makes you wonder what kind of foreign you watch
Well, I don't know
probably
You know, I like that. I like the BBC. I like the BBC
But I mean, yeah, I don't know if it looks real. I don't know. It's just like
Big
Like it maybe was like I'm missing the AI. I'm not saying anybody would even report it or really be offended
It's just like it was a little bit too
It was funny though. It's funny. Just make the next time just put on a little unicorn horn. Oh,
the point the point we made the same
You don't need to
Have a gigantic ballast, but I know everyone lives a gigantic ballast
It was linked to my leg. Yeah
The third leg, right?
Is that a link up here?
It's a link again, guys.
Okay, so Nick, so Nick, just because you did that, Nick,
I'm going to draw a picture of you.
But it's going to look like the picture of JT's.
Oh, so, so, so, hold on.
Here's a picture of Nick.
Okay, next
Okay, Nick are you there Nick? Here's your picture of Nick. That's what you got Nick
That's Nick Johnson
Pretty good
What was fun what was funny what was funny?
All right, I know I know I know the the we the wiener was fine. Okay, it's fine. I'll add a wiener to his
They weren't happy they weren't happy. Okay, I need to look
Okay
Tommy, can you hear me?
Hey, you didn't miss much.
Just imagine Nick with a third leg, you can pretty much.
You think you want to go skateboarding around?
Well, Nick, weren't you just arrested for skating around?
All your juice is just a Santa Claus,
and it was considered too much.
So why are you going to go around with that?
And then you're going to be arrested for public indecency
and all this kind of stuff, OK?
So don't even try it.
Oh, you still want to see the picture again? Hold on. I'll show you.
We can find it. Hold on. Let me see. Yeah, here it is.
I tried to give him a, I tried to, I tried to make, first of all, I tried to make him kind of a
phallus, like that shape. And then I like drew him in and stuff, but it didn't quite work.
Oh, you're welcome.
Oh, yes, well, you know, I were once at one time of Nick, I wore an American flag speedos
out, not in public, but on my stream, I mean, in front of everybody, I mean, everybody saw,
I mean, I was trying to show my patriotism.
I got a little bit exuberant.
You know, I thought it was funny to put my legs
behind my head and to like, you know,
pull it up my butt like I have a, I'm wearing a thong.
But it was, it's not a, it wasn't appropriate.
It wasn't appropriate.
So I'm sorry.
I'm alive guys.
I apologize for the, I apologize for the, you know,
but I'll wear, I'll wear the, I'll wear those speeders again.
Speedos gonna get guys. I saw it. I actually saw some guy with the same speedos. I have on it was he was like in an ad
Speedos she was hilarious, but they're gone unfortunately because some jerk
Poor mommy
Yeah, the only thing bet you guys my
Easy about that speedo and you you got yeah, it's like, you know
Easy easy easy about one speedo and the laughs will last forever
It was off to do now. I'll do it doesn't maybe the dress rehearsal stream
I'll do it again on July 4th. Maybe we'll see Milgo to the beach and do it. I don't know I
Get my bike fixed. Maybe I'll be in a good mood for that. Oh, it's a four-day shit
Yeah
We'll see what happens to my bike.
It'll be okay.
We'll see how I do without smoking.
Like I do have some tobacco on my table.
I don't have any cigarettes.
I don't want them either, but I do need to have a lighter,
because I got all this weed I got, and I have sage.
But...
salutes what's up the one jade James hi hey how's everyone yeah so I was like
well you know I was I watched some interesting stuff I watched some like I
saw some like some shows about like a month ago and people to it's just like
so amazing how
You know sometimes it's always good because it's like there's so you're coming so far sometimes and it's like
What can't be that was a month ago all that was happening now that now we're now we're here much better place, right?
But it was just like you know there's so much going on a month ago, and so much stress and now it's like, you know
How many bands this week? I don't really ban any of it. I mean I try to ban people
Unless they really they piss me off and some people do sometimes
Sometimes I just don't like to be played with
But
I'm usually very reasonable compared to especially compared to a lot of other content creators
Hell yeah, I don't see it. Oh, here we go
Yo, yo, yo, hey, that's me. That's me
You're me
Yeah, yeah, I will be watching you on the TV
I can't read the chat unless I see it on the TV man. My phone's is old
I'm old dude
It's okay. I'm gonna go to you. I think I'm a man. Hey, uh, I hope you're avoiding this heat man
Avoiding the heat. Yeah. Well, it's not too hot. I mean, it's everyone else who's been talking about the heat
It's it's not very hot here. It's completely
We got the same birthday exactly
January 7 1979
No, no, I'm I'm 80. Oh, you know, I'm a couple years later. I bet uh
No, no, no, no, I didn't tell you anything. I said, no, no, no, I'm a couple years. I am January 7. Yeah, I think I didn't
All right. Well, no, no, no, no, you're not how old are you?
How old are you?
Well, you don't have to give me exact age are you in your 50s cuz I'm 44
So I don't know if you think you're I'm not much younger than you
You're probably we're probably similar age. I think so. No, I'm I'm 47. I'm getting ready to be 47, bro
Okay, so we're three years or so years apart. We're close
Hey, everybody in chat
Hey, look and look at the Nick Johnson brother does that all the ducks are doing great. Hey, uh, but uh
Yes, yeah, we got some good people in your chat man. You always got good people around you
Yeah, I don't know why up miss shade used to have a wrench and I if you don't mind
I feel more comfortable having somebody that I know and trust having a wrench
If you well, you know a wrench well is it say it's yeah, well is she she wants she wants
It's your channel. Yeah. Yeah, she can she can mention to me. I've been very forgiving with you know, especially with no
I don't know. I don't know your models
Yeah, so maybe I don't know what happened. I is none of my business anyway. Hey, look
I did promise you I'm getting a day and I've looked it up
On the Amazon like you said, uh, there's a Star Wars. You said you wanted a Star Wars tarot deck, right?
Well, I mean I think I for $44 and then there's one for $32
Well, that's I mean
That's well, that's pretty expensive and it's like, you know what it's like
Like Star Wars I'm like really I've seen the I've seen this first Star Wars
I'm familiar with it in pop culture, but I'm really I like space balls
Star Wars on Star Wars. Yes, space balls. That's right
But I think they're coming out with a new space balls. You see that you just
They're making a new Spaceballs movie finally it's not gonna be the same without John Candy playing bar stuff
Yeah, John candy his barf is not he's dead. So yeah, and then it's like
Nobody yeah, I would say I would say you know
Chris Farley in the movie, but he's been dead for years as well. I mean, it's like these fat guys
You need to you need to like, you know, right that would have been a great reply. Oh my god, Chris Farley is bar
Yeah, that would have been great
But look, yes, I'd I'd feel more comfortable having somebody in chat that I know like I don't know none of the other my other than just miss Jamie
Jamie's Cowboys and he man
He man's also he man's also been a mod here since the beginning of my sir
Miss Memphis Shay time time was a good model you look. I don't know what's been going on
I honestly haven't caught everything. I've been working in
This heat man is killing me
It's he gets really hot. Well, you know, I hope you see. Oh, okay. So all right. Well, hey, he made
Okay. Yeah. Oh, yeah, he says or better. I'm sorry. Fuck a he made Skeletor is my dough
Well, I kind of look like just jokes. I kind of I kind of look like Skeletor. That's just kind of a rock
No, okay. So guys, I do so hold on. So there's a there is a deck a few decks
I see that I like and like one is called
the
Rebels I just thought it's called
You can't look like Skeletor. Well, aren't you be Skeletor? Let him be he made in a chat. Yeah
Well, I do kind of like it. So, yeah, well, it's called. It's I'm sorry. Yeah, it's it was there's called
it's the
It's called the Diablo the sanctuary deck and guidebook. I just need to make sure it's not it's like is it the it's not based on the
Play you know what? Uh, can I ask you to do me a favor? It is
Can you also link to it in your discord like yeah
Ooh, okay, I think I see I do see I do see one. Ooh, I see one. I really like ooh. It's looks really cool, too
Okay, well, it might be too expensive, but I'll open up your discord and Friday when I get my well
I'm supposed to get paid Thursday night at men though. Thank you
Fucking
That's a thoughtful
You know what I promised you did you know, you've you've been nothing but cool to me and
Yeah, yeah, and you know what I hope that I
Hope that every goddamn reading you make off of this deck is nothing but the truth
You know, I've always heard
Somebody gives you a deck of the tarot things. It's it's the way to do it. You're not supposed to bomb yourself
But if that's the one you want
Fuck it man. Let's get it. Hey, well, I you know, I think I think I found what I'd like. It says
They have a garbage
Thursday night, but I'll
Make sure money goes in the bank too far. I hate that they're doing this shit
They have a garbage pill kids deck, I mean, that would be pretty funny
You ever like the garbage pill kids? That's pretty they're pretty funny when I grew up on
What they have garbage pail kids tarot duck
Never seen that have you heard of it?
Garbage pail kids are like, you know, they're kind of like the trading card
Let's get it. Let's get how much is it? You like that one? Hey
Hockets
For the for the cards $17.60 for the car. Does it say how much or no? Yeah, it says $17
1760 says you can you can you can yeah, they have the either the just like and then they have like an option for hard
All right, how much it said what says no, I've never eaten. I love yeah
I love the garbage mail kids brother. I'm putting it on my wish list. It says
$17 in the 80s. Yeah, yeah
Okay, it's on my wish list. I put on the wish list
And there you go so you can
Yeah, please share that in your discord if if you get it. I
Will I will I'll put up a post my Amazon wishlist in my score. Thank you for reminding me
But I'll put a few I'll put a few decks
Discord and we're doing some garbage fail stuff
Okay, let's agree the garbage pail. Yeah
We're gonna have snot exit. We're gonna have smelly Kelly. We're gonna have all kinds of
Terror cards that are that's gonna be hilarious, brother. I love this. I love it. I love it
Oliver like that's gonna be awesome. Dude garbage pail kids
I'm with
You know, there's actually like there's actually also like there's like it's like fate in my garage
How do I do it? Should I just I want to send you the card so it's not like you buying the cards
I don't want to send you like yeah, I do is like if you mean the the Amazon wishlist
You know you go to the it will like you know if you can you can say you know send it send it to me
And it was it will send it to me. Oh, it'll look it's in your discord. So where do I go? I just go in there and
Um, yeah, I mean, yeah, okay. No, okay. Here's like
All you lovely people in chat, what up, what up, what up? Hey, but uh
Thanks for letting me on your panel, man. Hey, you're welcome. Hello, Billy. Thank you. You know, I love you
I think you appreciate you, you know
Help by the show
How Billy you're a good good friend of the show
My friends. I'll all call you his friend. Okay, but so if
The Amazon will send it to you if I buy it
Yeah, they'll send it to me. You can buy it. You can buy it for me for my
Just to go to my go to my Amazon list. Okay, there's like the link to it right there
Then uh, but you got it in your discord so that I can scroll back cuz I'm not
Yeah, be able to find I I got I got to put it in there or if a mod can put that in my discord much love brother
Yeah, we're doing a garbage pale kid tarot deck
Sounds great. I'm forward to it. Love you. Yeah, we're not friends. We homies. We it is what it is. You're good by me, man
Okay, thank you. Well, I
Yes, thank you
Always something look forward to you guys always every hilarious. Yes, we can, you know
It's like I like I like the
please
If you can that's how I can get it right if not. Oh
All right, man. Let me jump down my fucking phone sucks later. Okay. Okay. I'll talk to you soon
What how is that was like that?
Hi, Nichole. Okay, I'm gonna put, I'm gonna put, I have a turkey patty. I'm gonna put that in the oven.
Maybe I'll have a beer or two tonight, but ugh. I don't know if I'm gonna go pick up any more alcohol.
Everybody.
Yes, remember the fingers suck.
So let me see.
Hey, traveling gypsy. How are you? You're gonna have a turkey burger for dinner, too. Mm-hmm. Good
Yeah, hi, Nicole
Hey, Irby
Yeah, I did post the link though. Okay, link is posted
What's this book?
Ugh guys, I'm gonna start reading to you. You know, I have this book. I have this book. It's a very occult book
It has a pretty cool
It says in the first page it's called the zealot or it says in the first page it says it says
Etche man
Okay, so it says etche man, this is in Latin. It's etche man Patineur
philosophy
Fardum
Nobis, assumee, and that means, what shall we allow a fool to play philosopher with us?
And that is from Lucius Apolaus, the golden ass, as there is a picture, it's a cute little
picture.
He's kind of laughing.
So this is a modern and usually it explores the ancient mysteries.
So maybe I'll read some of this to you guys and we can just read a little bit at a time.
See it is very esoteric.
You know,
a lot of interesting information.
I just don't know the prologue is very long, but the first chapter is called the way of the fool
I look forward to reading that to you sometime. It says
There's a lot of very interesting stuff as it's the way it's called the way of the fool and this is like it's like the whole tarot deck is like the
Life it's like everybody's life. There's some interesting drawings here's
This is the prodigal son who's kind of like very similar to the fool. It's like a kind of archetype for the fool
Of course we have a new bus a new bus
With the body of Osiris
If you knew was a Scorpio, I guess the Scorpio the diacral Scorpio
This is some art by Austin, Austin, oh no, no, hold on. Yeah, Austin Sparer did some
drawings for Dante. For Dante is a Camarona or something that's Austin Sparer do that picture.
Interesting.
Hello.
Hey G. I
Don't think she hear me guys. Hi Paige. Can you hear me? How's it going? Good? How are you?
Can you hear me? Yeah, I hear you perfect
Is it not working? Can you hear me?
Hello
Hello, everyone hears you. Okay. It's the way you don't ask me. I like this. I can echoing on my phone. So I'm sorry
Okay
Oh, I hear Raven. Raven, are you talking to or talking?
Raven, you always have so much to say.
Mew, meow, meow, meow. Hope everyone is going through a hard time.
Everyone that's going through a hard time. Yeah, everyone makes it a hard time.
Yeah, so I just, I had, I took a little, you know, just a
It's kind of like a night the rest of the night off last night and just
been to sleep pretty early actually and
It got like a lot of my house cleaned and so then I came back today refreshed ready to go
And you know, it's always nice to have people asking for me and you know people are asking for me
Where are you? Where are you?
Nope, sometimes I might need a day off, but I'm gonna be here as much as I can be right guys
Yeah, the Ravens little diva or Raven it Raven and Lenore and you can become pen pals things
Pop house or they start talking on the phone. Yeah, yeah, it's our taking up our phone
Wouldn't that be something that would be
Yeah, we're all kind of worried about yeah, we weren't worried
We're just like we've none of us had heard from you in a while
And so we're all kind of just asking about you and trying to locate your make sure you were good. Yeah, well, you know
I'll always be usually okay. It's just like, you know, I
I
Go into her my mother. Are you at life path nine? I don't know if you are too or yours. You might be a sick
I'm not sure are you nine or
For a life path, you know your life path you're me, huh?
Um, yeah, what are you? What are you nine? What am I? I think I'm a
Shit, hold on. I'm gonna have to recalculate this. I haven't done it in a while
Give me two
No, I'm a five. You're a five. Okay
Yeah, if I did that correctly, yeah
Well, you know five like the five like the five
You know in tarot the fives in tarot, you know, they can be
It can be like a little bit more of a treacherous path sometimes let me see, you know the fives
Interesting and Sarah let me see it's life path five. It's definitely you but you might be if you if it's
If it goes to double digits, then you're the double digit, but I don't think it's bigger for five
So life path well
32 and then you and you add three plus two and then it's five, right? Okay. I think that's how you do it
Well
It says, life past five is one of resourcefulness, discovery, choice, change, freedom, and the
physical aspects of life.
You must learn by trial and error about your own physical presence and the effect your
presence has on others.
Five emphasizes your physical body, your sexual intensity, and the way in which your
body, mind, and emotions are able to adapt to change.
changes constantly and that you can either prosper from these changes or be overwhelmed by them.
Learning about the physical aspects of life is one of your main purposes in this lifetime.
It says there's only one success to be able to spend your life in your own way
and not to give others absurd maddening claims upon it. Christopher Morley. I like that quote a lot.
But it says being yourself being honest with your feelings and encouraging that same student spontaneity and others is essential
Five enables you to change your inner attitudes and outer appearances to suit different circumstances
This level of adaptability and enables you to be all things to all people and to fit in naturally to almost any situation
You cannot be comfortable if your behavioral pattern is consistent. You are ever-changing personality is who you are this
Take life as it comes quality is what makes others still relaxed around you.
It should never be curbed by your own or society's misconceptions about free expression.
It's been said that variety is a spice of life and it is your flexible nature which helps you
to experience more variety than most people.
What do you think? Do you have anything about that? Is that really to that?
Pretty excellent and spot on.
Yeah, it's pretty I think it's pretty cool if you study the numerology and astrology and tarot
You'll find like so much of it really resonates with our my camera's not blurry. Maybe it was my camera was blurry
Anyway, yeah, I did blip the camera. I'm sorry
How's that? Oh my god, it's not even it's not worse. Oh my gosh, oh shit
I don't know what's going on guys. It was blurry. I don't know why he's so blurry
My vision is blurry the cameras blurry now, it's blurry again
Okay, I think it's better
My gosh, you guys want to know what I did. I thought I had to work today
So I was getting ready for work and I don't it's next Monday that I work at this Monday off
Well, you know you work almost every day, so
Yeah, I'm gonna try it.
Is it better?
Spreading the oiliness, is it oily?
I don't know.
It's better.
I don't know, my phone keeps,
or my camera, or my tablet keeps falling on the floor.
And we sprayed a lot of fleece stuff on the floor yesterday.
I don't know if that's it or whatever, but.
All I need to do is clean my table then clean my bedroom and then and do my dishes and then my whole house is perfectly clean
Yay
Thanks guys, we're gonna spend some of it with y'all cuz like I
Don't feel like going anywhere. We live so far out of town. It's just like it's very muggy right now
And I just kind of wanted to stay home and relax. So that's kind of nice
Ooh, that was my old, my old babe still had a hit on it.
Hitting it, hitting it, hitting it.
You're better, as an unexpected surprise,
having a day off.
Yeah, isn't that nice?
It is.
Yeah.
Yep, that's true.
HK, HK, come on.
Let's see.
Yeah
I was thinking I was late like it's the one time I thought I was three time and it's late and I called my boss was
Super confused and she's like, okay question. We're kind of like I'll see when you get here
I didn't get there and I look at the schedule and I wasn't on till like two and I was like
I don't know. It's way way early super early, and I thought I was gonna be late
I've just been looking through these pictures in this book I have, it's an esoteric book.
I can show you the Stella Maris, which is like the star of Maria or whatever.
That's fine, but then it has other pictures, not so appropriate.
I'm not sure.
Oh, it also has, there's on a...
On some of the cathedrals, there's all these demons in these, like, some of these Templar churches and stuff like that for interesting astrological signs.
Devil card, then there's, let me see.
This is a devil card in the Thoth deck. I don't know if you ever read the Thoth deck, but there's a devil card in the Thoth deck.
And it kind of looks like though it's a little bit upside down, right? Oh, I don't know. Maybe maybe I'm not sure. Okay
This cool this called the Union of Isis and Osiris look at the black and the white United, right?
Yeah, I
Pretty beautiful
Good pagey. Yep
Yeah, grab a beer because now I'm allowed to have a beer
Awesome enjoy your beer. Thank you
Yeah
You wish you had Brune Shadda, what's that? Oh rum Shadda. Oh rum Shadda
Brumchata, this is a call from no one.
Bruheria?
Mm-hmm.
Brumchata.
Oh, hey, can you hail Billy?
You look at it.
Yo, you put a garbage pail, a care deck on the discord?
Okay.
I'll, uh, well, I don't know.
Because it's like, I can put, because that, no, it's like,
you have to go to my wish list or from the wish list.
Or else.
I think because there's this having a link because you need you need my wishlist, right?
So you want to use the wishlist can someone post the wishlist on chat or in the discord, please
My mod it can it's available. Thank you so much reminds me page
You have a desert tarot deck on your stream earlier. It was gonna come a bit. Yeah, you made your mods hate
Pothog. It says you have a desert tarot deck
Um, no hotkits. I don't have a dessert one. I wonder what you're talking about and also which who doesn't like you
Or which mod who do I have modded that doesn't like you because
Because I like you and you're welcome. I might always
Pages pages pages very cool. Oh, yeah, psyche and pay. Yeah, it's like a pay. Hey, what's up, Norvader?
Yeah, we got a great. Yes, it's the least of the guys round ones
It is Lisa Georgana's birthday. I see and she is on she's on live tonight shit. I would I need to I need to
Send her a message and I will be sure I will. I've just done it before nine. Yeah
Um, yeah, I love Elisa and I haven't talked to her lately because it's like her chat with her chat kind of turned against me
And you know, I don't want to bring problems to her show and I really use but
Cards are pinking around you have pink and round cards what which cards are those? Yeah, they're the they're the
the
tea leaf oracles the tea leaves
Oh, they're called the tea, the tea leaves, they're called the tea leaves, uh, and I think they do have a really cute, like, you know, one with some dessert on it, maybe, but, uh, yeah, oh, shit, my, my, my, uh, my turkey breast is ready, I'll be right back.
You're a turkey breast.
I'm a turkey, I'm a turkey breast.
Mm-hmm.
Ooh.
Who's the evil mod? Who's the evil mod, let me see.
Oh. Juice!
He's not here, I don't think, right now.
Yeah, I could give you a reading. Podhawk is with those one time. If you want, they're
really, they're quite neat. They just kind of have months, and, and like people, and
just, it's, it's kind of neat. They just have a bit more of, in them, like information-wise,
Okay, it's bye. Bye Jenny. I love you
Really good just pissed me off today. Anyways multiple times
I did it such oh, no, it's okay in Vader. It's fine. It's not like I gave warning that I was gonna quit
Up such a long life. I didn't mean to either. It's kept getting messages after messages
And I was like, okay. Well, I think we need to go back on because I went on once and then it was like half an hour
And then tried to do another one and then my phone died
So I have like a five-minute one to start of it and then and then like a two-hour one
My service is shit, so that might fuck it up, too
And I think it's better guys to have like less look more like less notifications for channels than that me and the unless you like
Really went up the bit like it goes live and stuff like that
Probably want a notification other because I think it will make you know once you start getting so many channels
I have thousands of channels
They start getting so many channels. They
They just sent a they sent a digest with a like a couple times a day with no
So and you never gonna see the notifications at that point anymore. So
Better to have less
Hannah, what are you talking about?
An odd thing to say
How are you feeling now?
We know you guys knows there's a no stalking policy on my on my channel, okay?
So just it's up. What's okay? What's still up?
What are you talking about?
I guess he did he stream something about saying that Hannah what are you referring to? I don't ever heard this this news yet
What's going on? Can you explain to Hannah?
I don't know if you know who Hannah is and all the drama we've had with Gaudi and Jaycee and Hannah, and a few other people, hold on, there's a few other people, let's see, oh yeah, there are people coming out of the woodwork I don't even know, I mean, no, no, it's not you, Hannah, it's not me, it's not me, it's not me, it's not me, it's not me, it's not me, it's not me, it's not me, it's not me, it's not me, it's not me, it's not me, it's not me, it's not me, it's not me, it's not me, it's not me, it's not me, it's not me, it's not me, it's not me, it's not me, it's not me, it's not me, it's not me, it's not me, it's not me, it's not me, it's not
I know and they're not here right now, but so I'm not sure. I don't think they're stalking you, but yeah, this is like, you know
I'm kind of I'm kind of being tongue-in-cheek like let's all get along. I think that's serious
People warned you about them Ella. Well, who but but yes, yeah, I know people wore me like what?
Lisa what?
What what do you say someone Hannah? What do you say? What do you say about my my friend, Elisa?
Hannah, that's not the real Hannah Hannah wouldn't say such thing because Hannah didn't hand a cancer survivor
But she's not gonna talk about Lisa and Emma talk about cancer like that
So I think she's maybe saying that Lisa's like a zodiac a cancer. Oh, yeah, she is. Oh, yeah. Oh my gosh. Oh my gosh
Oh, yeah. Oh, what is Emma? Hey, I know you're so much. I know it's not funny. How yeah, she's a zodiac because her birthday today
Actually, I was I'm so ridiculous. What is Emma?
I
Know guys, I'm embarrassed. I'm embarrassed. I
Don't know Emma's side Emma would never tell me her sign Emma. I always guess Emma was like an Aquarius or like a Scorpio
I know I know guys I just jump on people I was like I thought it was I thought it
was a fake panic and I was like because people I because then it means to say
people are just saying horrible things and so I'm just like I just think sometimes
I assume the worst. People call people call me a cancer and it's not in a nice
way. I'm sassy.
Yeah, well, I hope we give it you know what I like I like I like I like Gotti
But you know, he's he and JT has proven that they're not to be left
Unsupervised and now another Alex either you know for them. I mean, it's like there's a lot of people or it can't be
unsupervised on the show. I mean, it's like it's like the equivalent of like
Leaving I'm not gonna say the inmates and these I'm gonna say I'm gonna say you know, it's like giving like, you know
Some some random student in the school like the keys to the school and it's like
It's like you're like you run it you run it for the day and then it's like it's gonna be burned down, right?
It's always like
You have to like not I have to like not do that again
I'm trying to do better. I'm trying guys
God he posted a big piece picture piece of poop
JT posted a woman mounted by a dog or a dog mounted by a dog.
I'm not sure what it was.
It was just disturbing as hell.
And I don't know why he put it on my show.
I had to delete all the streams.
Guys, come on.
Stop posting.
Bestiality and disgusting things like that.
Why would you even think that you should put...
Can you...
No, please.
Daisy you're you're you're young warning now and Alex. I don't know where Alex is. What the hell is Alex
Loud on the show or not him. I'm not even I get so confused
everywhere
It's a revolving door. I'm not the most forgiving show the show and chat on YouTube officially. I
Have the most forgiving
Oh
Oh, who's here?
Hello
Hello, Dan Gard.
Good evening, Mr. Syke. Here it is.
Hello. Hello. Hello, Gumbna. Hey, what's that? What's it coming out of the tank? Is that a Chinese tank?
And what's that coming out of? What's going on? Is that Tiananmen Square? What's going on?
It's supposed to be a Chinese Russian tank in Tiananmen Square with beneath the poo over it.
Okay. Oh, okay. Okay. Sorry about that. My cat eating my burger. Okay. Well, yeah, well, that's that's that's that's that's
We just leave that there. I don't want to get too controversial
I was up here for a couple of hours, but everybody was talking and I didn't want to be accused of over talking too much.
So I just let them crack on and I cooked a steak, but I enjoyed your show, so you can wait and see.
Oh yeah, so Vanguard, so you like held down the four for like five hours.
Okay, so well, I have to say, you know, you're lucky because JT messed up that night.
even if you did something wrong he he over he you didn't do anything wrong
because he over shattered you so so so everything was fine i appreciate you
you uh you know you had some controversial topics and stuff but you
know it's my fault for leaving the show i appreciate you not for going too far
with it for being respectful on the panel and you're
absolutely fine and a welcome guest okay so it says that they're
I do have some Swedish ancestry, a lot of Irish, Scottish, German, and a little bit of some other stuff.
Okay, so yeah, I don't know.
Spick in the Dueschen?
Guten tag? I'm not sure. Actually, that's not very good in German.
Schwarzenegger. I just know our Schwarzenegger's name means something.
Thank you for the crap tonight. I've only just parachuted in, so what's the crap tonight?
We're doing good, actually. I mean, it's like, we have 20, 34 people in chat.
Where is Jen? I've been, you know, away from the show for like a little bit.
Everyone's get kind of nervous when I'm way too long
But I'm back better than ever
Tricks is eating my my turkey burger
And he's like you don't know tricks is my cat. He I have cats
Do I have this turkey burger for whole food? I'm gonna have to cover it up now
It's a sniper
Okay
Yep
Yeah, so Lord Bader is saying, holy crap, is that Vanguard?
Yep, that is Vanguard indeed.
He won it only.
The wolf is in charge the head house. Yes, it's like pretty yeah, it's like pretty like well
Yeah, that that's what it could suck you up
It's like I gave a my example wasn't very good because it was like I'm like if you put a random student at a school or you know a
Random like you know person that is like no this is like pretty someone that actually is a mischief
It's like give me giving it a key to like, you know
The bully the like the or the you know the school bully and then and then and they think that they'll sit there with you with the
authority of the red apple
in the dry erase board
That they have the authority of the show. They don't but okay. Yeah, but you know what it was okay
The show is fine. It was like, you know, I don't know if people were I
I think I have I think I have some divine intervention myself when it comes to the show
Why is there a bully though I?
Don't know and Ziggy you have to ask a JT and God because I clearly heard them bullying people
Several times
Oh, I mean do you think that you think they can actually bully not really just people just go fucking now
What a bunch of fucking in cell?
Homosexual pieces of shit to be honest, but anyway, that's my
Well, I mean, it's like, you know, you can think what you want about them
I think I'm not gonna say anything bad about them, but I all I'll say is like I've seen I've seen like kind of this
Wild just kind of wild bullying where it's like it's like it's kind of things that you wouldn't even think
to be cruel enough to do is
They've been doing them LD LD and JT I know
Set some mentally this disabled person up to go to Florida to meet some kind of
woman that he was in love with and then it was all a farce to
waste his time and
Let's get him to Florida walking around. I don't know. It just sounds very very
Very negative, but I do love Gotti. I do refuse to call him God
because
No, he's definitely not a god. He's a goat, a goat that goes for a cup of tea and brings it back to you, his wheelchair.
Goat to tea? Well, I'm the goat, I'm the goat, so he's bringing this goat some tea, it looks like.
Okay, yeah.
So who has my birthday? Oh yeah, Hellbilly does. Hellbilly and I have the same birthday, isn't that amazing?
Hellbilly and I have the same birthday, Tiger Butterfly and I have the same birthday, and you know, Tiger Butterfly doesn't bug me anymore.
That's way the same birthday.
Hi, you know Gotti for a very long time. He's like it's a mess off. He's a mouse up back and jt is the same way. Oh, I oh
I don't know if it seems it's a very it's a very odd crowd of people that you that you that you've chosen to
They you they that he vented a bullying. I don't know if you guys were all the same community or whatever and I went after each other like I
Mean because this is a hand out Hannah who has like, you know
You know, you know, she's the people kept trying to put the picture of her breast cancer
Scar removal scar up on the on my panelists, but you know we're harassing her and stuff. That seems pretty pretty out like that
You know, I don't know
What war war psyche psyche, can I can I ask her a question? Yeah
If somebody's saying something smart alecky to you
Are you just willing to be like?
Whatever or would you want to slap back? I
I can be like I can be like whatever because people say terrible things and like especially ignore people sometimes and not make the
You know escalate situations or try to like, you know
Perfect your answer is perfect. There are people in this world
Man that they'll just take it
And there's people in this world that are like, you know what? No fuck you, you know and
That's what I am and that's what you
Over talking you expect all those people without you process
without due process
I hope one day without due process affects you your piece of shit Ziggy
Whatever man, I'm I was talking and you're trying to overload it and say that that you were talking. That's terrible
That's see. That's exactly what I'm saying. There are people out here psyche that are
You know that don't put up with it and we're straight back
And that's real simple.
And I've known Gotti for a long time, man.
Since, like, what?
Since COVID?
No, no, no.
I know, I know.
But you're saying they're striking back.
I just can't see, like, where.
maybe like
I still I never heard Hanna did this to this the group Hanna did that to the group
And I just heard oh, you know Hanna was at this other panel
We knew and she's now she says this one and it's just like no one
Really don't know who Hanna is, but I can tell you this and I mean this
I've never seen Gotti or JT or Vader
Go after somebody with an illness an impairment, whatever it may be
Unless they were attacked first. That's all. No, it was I think it was rusty like rusty like
Got the picture off the face
To me it sounds like a load of jack-o-n-orey bullshit to me
Can you smell?
It might be what that is to you vanguard, but I'm telling you
that I've never seen it, ever, never, and and by the way people seem to attack JT
with like pictures you know that psyche they're like oh my god he docks me dude
I've never seen him do that those people put their pictures up themselves saw it
okay witnessed it
Yeah, I know but the GT what or no, that's it. You're not GT. Okay. I'm sorry. Okay, so never mind. Yeah
You guys confuse sometimes so people are saying you're straight up lying ziggies on their panels float full blown out lies
Well, I don't know. Maybe maybe he's excited. I don't know. It's it's his perspective
I'm actually
Not an awful cocaine now, and I yeah, I do drink every once in a while. Yeah, for sure
How long were you on cocaine for?
Oh shit, dude. Is that a real question? I can answer it
Are you okay?
Okay, okay good
15 years. Okay, if you're on for oh, yeah, okay. Well, you know what? We've all experienced some kind of addictions and isn't it great we can like
Addiction man. It sucks. Yes, right. I hit my I smoke tobacco. I'm trying to quit tobacco right now
I know dude. I smoke cigarettes like it's fucking going out of the style. I hate it
Maybe you should get yourself some hand-rolling tobacco to not cheap it and I do I do that and then but then like I want the real one and then I go and buy is you know
that and
But I'm just coming up here, man. I'm not trying to cause a problem with even Vanguard. I know oh dear. Oh dear
I'm not trying to cause a problem with you
Fucking they're not that bad. Yeah, see look at that. Look I raised chickens and he just called me a chicken choker
Well, no, I didn't pick on you. You're a stick
You raise chickens in me
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
He knows that I choke and that I that I actually own chickens. Yeah, you're being absolutely ridiculous
Well, I I own some chickens too
You're a chicken choker is what I said
Come on. I took their heads off and I give it to the poor and I give it to uh, the four you give it to the four
I do. Yeah, and then but I
You give your
You're dead chicken to the poor you're dead. You're chicken
I butcher them and then I give you oh you do you oh you butcher them yourself and you hand out your cutlets to the poor
Okay, it's very interesting. I'm learning so much about you every day. Oh my gosh
Well, he's a chick Ziggy Ziggy's you know selling or these actually he's selling the eggs
But he's selling the eggs for $20 $20 a dozen, but he's giving the chicken away
Oh, you can hear the prices.
Ziggy Ziggy chokes his chickens. He likes to choke the death before he cuts you
Okay, well
Everyone everyone's chicken. He's a good choking every once in a while. I suppose. Okay. So anyway, he
It's okay
Why are you little actually he went up? He'd either keep it a lot of yeah
Well, he's not allowed in the D knows and like JC knows and God he knows no changing your photos around and every other people do it, too
I'm like
I mean unless it's something like I'll find new, you know, then I'll change my
Yeah, I
I was confusing you I was confusing you with a JT again. Oh, yeah, yes, prairie preach. Where are you from in the states of America?
Where are you from? I actually live in... Oh, go ahead. Sorry. No, it's okay. My apologies.
No, I live in Alberta, Canada.
Alberta? Fucking lovely. Nice one. I've been to Alberta. Do you know a place called Medicine
Yes, we got we're international on this show what we got just on this chat alone. We have Canada, America
England, where are you from?
Mars
Okay
Well wish at least in Jordana happy birthday. It's her birthday tonight the fuck would be that too and she's vouched for them
But that's how shameful there, but you guys went after beta too. What's going on guys? You went after beta Ziggy
What are you doing with beta me?
No, I've known I do bro. I've known beta as long as I've known Gotti
No, that's a dude. I was just over on a chat man and Sam. What's up?
Like you like he's like, what's up, man? Like we all fucking play around and say
I mean the cues cues he's been saying terrible things about me like terrible
It's okay, you know, I get called by other people and stuff, but he is like a stream
I don't like I don't like having
Yeah, Aldi also talks to horrible things about me. I mean, it's like but you know, I
Gotta keep on
Everybody will Aldi 1k talks horrible things about Q and me and then fucking we say hi
Let's put the OD is a failed I or Ella. It is a failed person. He might have sucked Andy's dick
Who knows made it in the captain contents fucking RV, but that's about it
He's an asshole. He drives his car drunk and smoked and he also drives his car when he has
Epileptic fits he's the piece of shit
He's a total asshole and he likes to go back
Why are you bringing him LD right now? We were talking about Q and other people
What are you doing?
That's the crack with LD. He's a field art narcissist. He's a poser just like John says. He's an arsehole.
Would you like him in charge of your elderly parents?
elderly parents in some sort of Jewish fucking Italian
Motorhome, sorry retired home
What would you like him fucking being in charge of them fuck off?
No, I would not but I mean and I necessarily mean I don't know if he's I don't know if he's a bad guy or not
Like but I mean he's been on the show. He's just not he's not a very interesting guest
He kind of like sits up here and like
Just talks in a monotone voice and says hi. He's like I'm a nurse and I have a cute dog
And I say that's that's that's the whole stick. I mean, it's like he's he I mean, it's cool
I love nurses. I love dogs, but it's like that's all he's said pretty much
When he showed you his ID of a field fireman tablet it's burnt apparently but again
He drinks and drives smokes and drives is an asshole
And what's he doing in charge of all people?
I'll ask you that question.
Yeah, but that's what I was saying is like he is I don't really care about that kind of stuff
But whenever you were thinking like somebody apparently to me
It sounds like somebody got to you about like JT and Gaudi or something and that's really no
No, I know it wasn't it was like I fell asleep one night and then like the first that night about that I fell asleep
You know Gaudi was up here with JT and then you know JT sort of started putting up
putting up a
pictures of people again, I don't know if it was Tiffany wears t-shirts or something like that and
and then and then he put up a picture of bestiality actually a picture about like a
Looks like a
Rottweiler writing writing a woman's woman's piggyback or something like that, but it's like I was all zoomed in
I can't tell what it was people had to zoom in and explain it to me
So yeah, so he's using beast he beastiality. He's like report this bi tch and then
He um and then the next night and so that was like for time I fell asleep with my phone and uh the next night
God he was on and I sent out and
And I didn't have a problem with what really god he said
I didn't like hear all of it
But I just like all I saw was he put a big
He put a toilet bowl with a big piece of poop and it was just like really gross
It was just like not it's not like it's not it's not it's just like it's not like
It's not I love it's bad for to us or not. It's just a it's just it's funny
I like dude if I were in a stream and I'm done
I've done it twice, you know, like that was back in 2000 like what 19 when
What it came up and fucking done that oh my stream dude, I would have left my ass off
Well, you know, it's like it was like it was the next morning
And so I would have like maybe said oh, and I probably would maybe would end the stream early, but it's
Okay, so it's like, I know people could just put a milky way candy bar in them.
Exactly. That's what I mean. That's what I mean, dude. One time. Look, let me put it this way,
psyche. One time, dude. And I'm willing to fucking say this, man. I'll say the truth. I was in a
relationship. Okay.
had a baby with us
What's that?
Fucking anyway, I was with this girl had a kid and every day man was a fight
with me going to work and
Knowing that fucking she's gonna be listening to her mommy all fucking day
And I got to come back from work and fix everything
Do you see what I'm saying? My point is is that don't let people whisper in your ear about somebody learn people for yourself
You know what I mean?
Right. Well, I know I know I know but yeah
Sorry, but me, I've had many talks, and he doesn't know his weapons, and he talks like
he's bumble all the time, so.
Right, because you like his vanguard.
Wait, what is?
You interrupted me, man.
I'm sorry.
I was going to say that.
Oh, he, he, vanguard interrupted me twice and complained.
I know vanguard you are into that was let's say Sun Tzu right Sun Tzu are you that person that's into the art of war or something
Or that a different person. I'm thinking maybe that's a different person
I am the spear of the tip of the spear on the universe and Valhalla in everything you think of
Okay, here we go. Okay
Okay, yeah, is it my turn is it my turn vanguard to use your word? Oh, dear. Oh
Thank you, Valhalla. Oh, dear
But do you understand what I meant by that psyche like what guess what I guess what I ended up doing now
I always took I always took that into consideration and I went and talked to you know her mom
Stuff like that, you know, so can't just go by ear is what I'm trying to say
No, I mean I would say
Most of this is not anybody's business. It's like saying, oh well, you know
It's just I mean just because I talked to people and I'm like, you know about there
I might say your name and people's name is like it's not it's like, you know Julia Roberts might answer might might like respond
You know if you talk to her in public too, it's like but
But it's not like that doesn't mean they all of a sudden they know
You can go after
You know the me and stuff like that. I don't think that's necessarily the the I don't think that's necessarily what's happening
By the way, bengar that was your burp was like literally like a three out of ten man. It wasn't a great
But what I mean, that wasn't the burp that was an elbow opening. Fuck, you know
Sound like a burp on our end. It sounds like a burp, but
So I think that what people are supposed to do is learn each other, figure out each other,
and then make the assessment. You know what I'm saying? And not just jump to what other people
say. Right, but there's some people that have like, you know, it's like, it's like getting a tip.
I mean, if somebody knows somebody for a long time, yeah, it's like, oh, they can, but it's also something that narcissists will do, they'll like, they'll come in, like, you know, and spoil the first impressions for everybody, and they'll come in and swoop in and like, you know, do whisper campaigns and stuff.
Think about this, like, I'm not even a part of it, and I'm telling you that I know Gotti.
know he means completely no harm I know I know I know that's why they're
still here he's having fun yeah but it's like we can't have fun at my expense
though it's like you know it's like you're we're all supposed to be having
fun together everyone's supposed to be getting into joking when up whenever I
was here I didn't see him say anything bad about you at all
what man
Yeah, you don't have to say you don't have to say something, you know, I said like, you know both appear to
I'm catching on that you don't like
Actually
But he ended up man. He grew on me man later as a good dude. He really is well
We know which places you go to Ziggy, we know what you are I don't know where I go
Well, I mean like the vanguard I can go anywhere mate and nobody can stop me
And your folks information of folks fucking no more jack shit is
Anyway
Yeah, but Laura Vader, but there are a lot of people you're saying people can't take a joke
That's what it is. He's not wrong
I know but you may know but you haven't you haven't you haven't been talked to like I've been talked to like you know
It's like, you know, you don't you don't
What are you talking about? I got my ass beat when I was a kid by my parents man
No, no, no, I mean, yeah, I mean I'm talking about talking I'm talking specifically about how
I get people are treated how people are dox, you know doxed and you know, I've been doxed and slandered and just people
It's a terrible thing. I'm not gonna have the LPL sensor about it man. I can see what I
Like you just said a while ago that you're learning more about me. I'm learning more about you
Because you mind me of an old friend well, yeah
I don't know why he's doing this. Why are you interrupting?
What?
You remind me of an old friend?
No, I was talking.
That's the problem with you, dude.
Vanguard, you're a woman because you're not supposed to.
You got to equal it out.
You remind me of an old friend.
what I mean come on your IRL buddies would you I be to always
I'll never win IRL ever in my life
You still don't know what weapons are you still
You want to school me on that then are you sure what weapons are the are what kind of
You know, the biggest weapon we can put on somebody is their own self, if we turn people
up against their own selves, if we get into a discussion about it, not only new NATO but
I know foreign too, yes I do, 7-6-2, oh yeah, and that's how you're going to do it, or if
Good and clear with Psyche is I can be, but you keep interrupting me while telling me that I'm interrupting you.
And that's what's important to me.
Yeah, old deer. I know. I know Vanguard. He's an old deer person.
So what I'm saying is, Psyche, I'm trying to put up the...
of showing you what, you know, Vader myself.
Okay, but I'm not gonna be, oh, Vader be my friend.
I mean, I don't know, he's in the person in the chat.
I don't know, he's not mean, not nice.
He doesn't come on the panel.
I really have no opinion.
Because he doesn't really-
Don't tell him to come on the panel.
No, he can't. Everyone's invited, but he can't come up if he wants to talk to me.
But I don't know. He seems like he likes the show, but he doesn't like me,
which is really weird, because this is my show.
Well, but I know that I know. Do you know how I know that JT and Goddy likes you?
the
No, you were you were here before like, you know the troll armies, but there is they you know
There was posted on some kind of
Troll just I think you're genuinely cool, and that's why I'm having this
Conversation with you, you know
Yeah, but you just said to the public about don't go to you take go fuck yourself
What type of human being that's the thing that's what I mean psyche right there dude you can't have
other people influencing you on what you should like that's the problem
in my life dude I've noticed when I was younger I was influenced now I'm older and I'm good no
Right, but influence is like the flu. It's like influenza. It's like, you know, it's like people get influenced and and then they
Then their opinions about it. Oh, you want to do that? Okay. Well, how about believe in the middle of it is lie
You know, like come on. We can't we can't keep making up these little things with words. I know
Yeah, and you know, there's you know, there's no such thing as impossible the word itself says I'm possible
Yep, yeah, I know there's all kinds of shit out there. Yeah, it's weird
It helps towards a set off. I understand but you know, I go with instinct
I go, hey, you know what? It's like he's never done anything to me man. He's really cool, dude
I don't why don't do things that I don't I don't do things to people, you know, I rather than try to like try to bless them and they
Believe in like second chances and stuff like that. Oh, I believe in oh my god
Chances I believe in a hundred chances. I believe it's like people will fail again and again
We should shut it down and say hey
You know
I'm just saying they're they cause all this all these problems or these controversy occasionally, but you know
But I'm I'm I think tomorrow. They're oh, they're all still
But that's what I'm saying is that this is all I'm saying is that you see it and then what happens is you say it
And then all your friends are going and they're enemies and my enemies
Are going oh, yeah, fuck them like look at vanguard right now with me. He's like see
You you all have you all haven't been
You all haven't been talking about
Bita and me on their podcasts or like, you know, or trolling us on our own show. I don't know talk about you
I
Can see this I said because remember that one time I came up and I was like man, I'm not usually like this
I don't really want a mod
But I want one because to protect myself remember that
Yeah
No, but it's like yeah, I remember that's that's right
But I don't that's what I don't I don't want I don't want the mods to be that for that anymore
I want I want I want to have mods where that I can trust that are not gonna skin it like
No, no, we're not no at all because I've had he man, you know, I've had Jamie's Cowboys
I've had you know traveling gypsy. I mean look at the name. I've had
What, it's a man to A, I'm a member too.
No, he man, it's a very masculine man.
Oh, he man, he's a good one, yeah, he's good, yeah.
I just have I like that a few mods and the no one's gonna go after you like, you know
I thought you said see man, I'm like
Of course somebody's gonna be terrible to you
No, no, there's no there. You're thinking raging semen you're thinking raging semen, but it's name
Yeah, yeah
My god
Like I guess Q doesn't like you and I was over at Q's earlier today and fucking he was like
Yeah, fuck that God and I went like this. This is what I got me. He's a talk that guy about me
Right, and I'm
Yeah, I was even around waiting. I can't leave my name out of his mouth. Okay. What's what he said?
What he said exactly just a thought hold on one second
This I'm gonna tell you what I said in response in the chat
I was just in the chat. He was walking to like a McDonald's or something and I went
You know, man, I think it's like he's cool, but at the same time
That's what I said. That's me being at the same time. What it is. Yeah, like it's like
Where you were like telling me like man, I can't protect myself with a mod and shit
And so that's why you're so you're still you're still you're still mad about that. Okay. Well, you know what that's why I did away with most of the month
No, I know but you know, but you're man, but you know what? But you know what of Jamie's Cowboys? She will protect you
Okay, you know and he man too. They're very strong
Okay, he was there he man saw me say it
They'll play that with him, man.
They will protect you, OK?
They will protect you in chat.
I think he man will.
No, he's wondering.
We're going to have you in a little bulletproof glass booth.
It's going to be like DT's safe space.
It's going to say Ziggy's safe space, Ziggy's safe space.
And then
Like that's why that's the only reason I asked for a month
Now it's now it's different just don't so stop asking for it. See you're nervous. I know I don't
Know you're never gonna get a fucking timing me out and shit. No, you're never gonna get it. No one's timing out
I don't think you've been timed out one time since I have been
Yes, I have times you are who you guys who's timing to sign in JT out
He-Man or Jamie's Cowboys are the only mods I see in the room right now.
What are you doing? You guys, what are you doing? You're taking off Ziggy. Come on, guys.
I'm just kidding. I know they're not doing it. Ziggy, you're delusional. Imagine psyche has been
cried. I'm not delusional, man. I know. It's really happened and you were really high, I think,
and you weren't paying attention or something. I don't know, and I'm not sure. Maybe you were drunk.
I don't know.
And that's what the only reason because guess what man, I don't like to be a lot. I hate being a mod. I hate it
I don't know thing that I don't know. I think I think spunky is cool with God
Yeah, I don't know if that was the issue. I'm not sure that that's true. I'm not sure
I'd like to see everybody in here do the seawalk
Okay
Okay, well, you know what? You know what? Yeah, you know what? You know what? You know what? Um
We're not gang affiliated. It's not West Side Story. We're not going to do any gang dances or I'm not going to get shot over wearing blue, blue or red. Okay. I'm we're not going to do that here. We're always where you can say be this kid. He's gay. You can say psyche is gay.
I don't want to hear about the Crips. Okay. Thank you.
All right. My apologies. I didn't think it would be too personal. My apologies. But it's just my not to the fuck.
now i can read it in red i mean come on do you want me to go total fucking knowing my knowledge
in part and some knowledge you're not ready for the vanguard in that manner so i'll just let you
know it's exactly vanguard okay listen that's not a threat because vanguard's been around for
fucking literally four years and never saw you do a thing well okay well
I don't know
Can I get a little promise from you? No
Oh, yeah, I'll give you I'm giving you a chance and why you're also around
None of you are blocked you and blocked at all. I mean, it's like you're fine
Really upset me the other night what you did
You want you want as you want a special you want a special you know what you want a little special protection
You want some protection in my cat you got a you got to get a membership and then the membership says
That's five dollars that goes to your protection, you know, that's how that's how that's how that's how that's how that's how that's how
That's me. That's and that's how we do it around here. That's how we do it right
No, now you're sounding like you know, no, no God. God. He taught God. He taught me these are God you taught
He taught me how the mafia works
Good tea, can't even pick up a packet of tea. No, that's not that's not that's not true. I saw dude
I saw I I still oh
What do you mean fuck off what do you what is your deal dude?
I'm saying
I know
You have a membership and you maybe you'll get awarded a gifted one, but you have a membership your name
Yeah, and then I'll have a little black cat next to your name and that black cat is that's Lenore and she's an award
I mean capitalism on freedom is speech. That's very dull on Trumpish, isn't it?
But are you going to be locking people in?
You don't know anything about that because you're not in this country, so you're kind of weird.
But how many free readings have you given them when they ask every time every time? I mean, you know
But they're on the way they're on the panel. Yeah, well, I know I know now they haven't been I don't think I don't think any of them
Have donated anything, but but you know, I do appreciate them being here
Disrupting psyche, what are you doing?
But I see the shit all the time, Ziggy knows me. Psychic. Psychic. I mean, psychic.
I do know you. Psychic. Psychic. Psychic.
It's not really quite a feat.
What?
Oh, Lord. Now, are you going to tell me that you opened up a bottle right there? That was you burping again?
Yeah, that wasn't burping.
It was kind of like a force a little bit forced, but it's not maybe okay
The last time he did the same thing and he went, you know, I'm putting up a bottle
That's the only point you can't lie about if you lie about the little things then you're gonna lie about fucking
Who cares if you like who cares about the little me lying with the little thing what you do you care about liars
What is this
What's up? You lie all the time
Why don't you hush why don't you hush well well grown men are speaking
That's the first word I've said in two minutes. That's the first word. I've said in five minutes
That was like he's that true. Is that true? Is that the first word he said in five minutes? I
Don't think I don't think it's true. No
You have more of a Scottish accent, right? You just sound Scottish. You just hear something more Scottish than British.
Jury is in... okay, okay, hold on. What's up? What's up? Okay.
Everybody in chat. Hopefully we're doing good in chat. I don't know. It's just controversy.
I mean, I think you guys are good people. Like basically, but I think, you know, I think, you know,
Charles Manson has a good person in there somewhere, right? So it's like, I'm not maybe the
Yeah man somebody thinks Marjorie Taylor Greene's a fucking nice person. Oh my god. Marjorie Taylor
Greene is an awesome person. What the fuck? Okay I don't know who these people are. Yeah I don't
know if these are political people or celebrities. They're the only celebrities that matter. These
Oh
Guys is it Brian Austin greens sister
She's not that famous never mind. She's trying to philly bust her in talk. She's quite famous in europe
if you don't pay attention we do Marjorie Taylor Greene is very famous whatever I'd rather listen
to her for 27 hours than that Cory Booker dude that guy suck I'd rather listen to Marjorie
you don't know about she's Jonathan Taylor Thomas's sister Jonathan Taylor Thomas
if you bought for me, what's taking now? Hey, guys, what's going on? Guys, guys, look who's on my
guys, this was on this is on my you that was on my YouTube screen. Is that um is that that's the
Yeah, this is on my feed
I'm sorry. Okay. Um ice baby. Oh, yeah. So are we open?
Well, thank you. We open the giving Ziggy and JD and all of us
again. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Just be yourself. Just be yourself.
Thank you. No, no, nobody. No, nobody. No, nobody. I mean,
it has to be very different. It's gonna be hard. Okay, but
can you promise me? Can you promise me I'm protected down
there though? Again, one more time.
Yeah, no one's gonna bother. No one bothers. He man's got my ass is what you're saying
And who's the other one you give me a girl?
Jamie's Cowboys. I think so. Yeah, Jamie's Cowboys is nice. She'll protect you and
Samantha Avery too. She's cool
Yeah, we miss cowboys. Do they come from a brook back? Um
No, I mean, they are kind of, they're, they're football players, so they're kind of gay,
they're kind of gay, but they're in a more, you know, socially acceptable way.
It's all much the ass slapping in tight pants. No, okay
You should see rugby rugby and you know soccer that's much more gay than football
Samantha was the worst
Run rugby they're hugging each other's butts the entire game
So I use that I use a euphemism the correct for you proper soccer peers are not
All these people that tell you about us they're the ones telling you to shut the fuck up
You're just upset, Ziggy. I'll just choose a moment. No, I'm not. I really am not upset.
Now the attention's on me, Ziggy. You're just sick on you, Ziggy.
No, but that's for the day. I'm not upset. Ziggy, Ziggy, Ziggy, can't you see?
Sometimes you lose the sick. How about you nap before you end up with the chicken army on your ass?
Uh, yeah. What?
It was pretty good. How was your day?
It's gonna be a normie of course. Oh, that's right.
That's what Van Gogh is talking to me.
Oh, I got it before he came on.
Oh, wait, wait, wait. Let me guess, let me guess. Did he say what?
No, he said, he said, oh, the chicken choker.
Oh, God.
I know. And by the way.
No, wait, wait, wait, wait, please.
Jan owns chickens too. Yeah, I do my my family has chickens too. We're all chicken
You are I want to invest with you guys I wouldn't invest with you guys in a chicken
You know when you accuse us of a fucking chicken, you know that bit that's not
like nobody's hurt by that first of all. Second of all, like, is that really where your mind goes?
Like, do you automatically think, oh, somebody's got chickens, they must fuck them, huh?
Oh my god, nobody does. That's only Ziggy's, because Ziggy's into the colt, and that's what they do to chickens, they do that, and they do that.
He's a Satanist. He's a Satanist.
Okay, that doesn't mean that he sacrificed his chickens.
Well, they don't really care about animals.
They don't really care about animals that much.
Well, but that's not him, though.
Oh, that's Christian.
What the fuck?
Yeah, are you kidding me psyche? Are you joking right now? Chris K?
Chris K willing to show me his tattoos. What's what's what's what's on your tattoos?
Hey, did you know that me and Ziggy had a baby? Oh you did what's his name?
Church. Oh, how cute. He's such a good boy. A little gray. I love a little gray cow.
What is it called? Is it called the Rhode Island Red? Yes, the Rhode Island Red.
With a little bit of pink and purple on its head. The fact, Rhode Island Red.
Oh, dear. What are you talking about, Vanguard? That was the cat.
that's not that's not a red that's not our that wasn't European accent. He thought it was a he thought it was a he thought it was a red chicken. He's a great cat.
That's fucking rough dude. He has like two main words and it's oh dear and oh lord. What? And what? Yeah hit it yeah. Oh what? Yeah what? Yeah what? Yeah the three.
Listen, they come back when you learn how to speak English when you're over here with your mother your fucking accent like nobody fucking
He does speak English, but
Look, look at the chickens. Look at the chickens words. Motherfuckers over here rumbling like a fucking idiot
I'm gonna go down to the pub and get a pint like you sound like an idiot
That's his language, I mean that's his dialogue
What? See what I mean? Chris already knows, I've absolutely written his name.
Shameless eyebrows, he's drunk, he's drunk.
He never got fucking paid for it.
You know what Chris? Shameless eyebrows for $50.
Oh, you're fucking...
She have your eyebrow, Chris.
She have your eyebrow right now.
Oh, my God.
Like fucking, dude.
I'm not going to do anything.
You're a mom anyway.
She have your eyebrow right fucking now.
She have like a fucking wanker.
She have your eyebrow.
I'm not a fucking wanker, really.
share if you're right bro right now for $50
I do want Chris to sing a limb biscuit song real quick
bitch can you do it go for it
Yeah. Listen, I'm not wrong.
I'm not wrong.
I'm you know, I'm you know, I'm
you know, I'm you know, I'm you
know, I'm you know, I'm you
Take those those are probably people are trying to find those black black
No, no, because that's they're called they're called black cock. That's what they call the mail
But we're not gonna be sly. That's my woman
Yes
That red and white one that's
on top of the water feeder.
That is actually a rooster.
Chris is just jealous that the
black hawks are bigger.
I know what he's saying.
Are you jealous?
They're fucking us.
What the fuck?
If you guys want to get fucking
some like disease for meeting
black cock eggs, then have fun.
Gross.
You're definitely gay.
You ain't going to.
No, it's guys guys just keep keep the black cock out of your mouth
Like all my chickens that like have white eggs
They actually don't think they have one that lays black eggs
No, like I have I have
Hold on Chris. I have where all in reds man, which are obviously lighter than a black Dominic and
Fucking they lay dark red eggs and the Dominic's lay like a really light
egg
Yep
I thought there was a special like
Really expensive breed of chicken that lays that does well, you know, yeah, there are but you know, you know
You know what you have to get do you have that catalog?
Like I was on Martha Stewart
I'm reading the name of the catalog now, but there's a cattle a mail order catalog where they have all the different chickens
I can look okay. No, there's not I don't think a solid black eggs. I mean it sounds like
So kind of like, I want it now.
And then it's like, there's a rotten egg, maybe,
but people even make belute and everything.
Okay.
Even if they fucking Vanguard's gonna try to jump on you too.
He's dumb.
Yeah, but Martha Stewart is a point of information
when it comes to chicken chickens.
Okay.
Listen.
Okay, so, so guys.
Robert, put the fuck up.
guys it's interesting because it says it says it says there are black eggs but
it's it's just a regular chicken eggs boiled in sulfuric acid or
sulfuric hot spring water turning the shells black while the inside remains
normal it's a shell it's a shell so it's the inside is a bit normal yeah yeah
Yeah, but yeah, but it's in the chicken, the black chicken whenever you buy it.
How about an ostrich egg?
Black meat, nothing.
Would you eat a belute, would you eat a belute, a belute, Chris?
Okay, did you have a belute?
It's like, it's like.
There was a, there was a salmon, you know, but the embryo in it, I've heard of that.
Yeah, the duck embryo.
The duck embryo with the beak, there's a whole beak in there.
It's chewy and stuff.
There you go, I'm gonna do that.
No.
I
It'll make great it'll make several almost actually it will make by like eight almost
Oh, it was in Africa because no, I did all she takes on that it was in fucking San Bernardino in the goddamn cone pass
The other
I don't know. I think I think somebody somebody's had a little bit, you know, somebody's had a lot of fun
No, he's having fun. I don't know. I don't like how people have fun. People have fun
It's not funny
Okay, I have this I have this gay friend this big guy
You want to meet him?
I don't know if I want to meet other people.
He's from Portland, Oregon.
He's gay.
He's unsurlicized.
OK, well, I mean, I really don't care about that.
I don't care about that.
I don't.
I'm sure there's a very nice person.
I don't know if they want to come to my show,
they're welcome to type in the chat.
Otherwise, I'm not going to be pursuing.
Well, here's the thing.
I guess like a brown skinned of like, uh, uh, okay.
Well, I'm something I'm already disqualified.
Okay.
Oh, well, okay.
So, hey, sweetie.
That was fun.
Well, I don't know.
You have a discourse.
You know what?
It's like, I was going to tell you, like, people dealing with
people on YouTube is like going to AA.
You got to take people one day at a time.
My fight was on the day before
No, you are completely wrong when I went to a it was like yeah, you don't have to speak your name
But if you will that would be appreciated and it's in a church and I'm
And they come to me and I'm like I was just saying that it was one step at a time like one day at a time
One day at a time that was the only
All my paperwork and get it signed and get it out of here. Fuck that
Boy okay nevermind. Okay, so what?
Hey, that's what I'm saying. I'm moving bro. I'm out of Vegas. I'm gonna go by the beach. Okay, you're gonna go
Yeah
I can't remember I can't remember his name and the one that harbored Andy dick or whatever what the fuck was his name
Yeah, Wappy. Yeah fucking you guys aren't are you guys hanging out making music or anything anymore?
That's what that's my bed. That's one of my best friends out here Vegas. Yeah, he's my homie for sure
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah, you don't leave him not make music or just probably going to transfer it across the internet or whatever
I mean, he's you know, he's he lives he lives out of Henderson, which is like right by you know,
Vegas, but yeah
Which by the way, he's a fucking he's a bet to
Oh, okay. Oh, a veteran. Okay.
I remember talk to him, though. I haven't talked to Wappy.
Hey, listen, is Paige here? I want to say what's up.
Paige is here. Miss Paige, pray, Paige, or you're here.
I guess she stepped away for a moment.
Speaking of that, I went to the vet today.
Yeah. Yeah, I did. Is everything okay?
Yeah, everything, everything's fine, but it was, it was a really fucking stupid move on my behalf that ended up costing me about $200, but he's, he's fine.
I would have rather taken him and made sure that he's okay and nothing's broken then.
What, for you, for you, what, your cat or dog?
My cat.
Oh, what happened?
I don't want to say it
You know she has a dog Jesus
Yeah, you know what, but you know
Is it a cat or a dog because I didn't know either way he doesn't know that I have a dog
Okay does now might have been a chicken
It can be it can be a kick it can be a turducken for all we know who knows who knows if she's an animal
You know, we see we see yes chickens. We just pretend it's one of those okay, but I
Went to the gas station to get a sandwich on my lunch break and I came back and I I didn't
I didn't see him like the sunshine was shining in through the carport and it was like
Really really bright in there and I didn't see him and apparently I
graced him with
So yeah, we went to bed this afternoon.
Are you serious?
Yeah
I wasn't I wasn't even going fast either like but he's okay like nothing's broken. He's just sore
I'm still really bad, but it was I mean, you know, yeah, you better feel bad you fucking hit your car
It's not like I saw my cat and gas it like
Pay your fuck pay attention. You fucking hear you hear your goddamn cat fucking bitch. What a dumbass
Why don't you pay attention to whatever the fuck you're doing over there and don't fucking
I already got it. I already got a man to tell me what to do. I don't need you. I don't need you
Don't worry about her. She's fine. There's a what there's a what there's a there's a woman
There's a woman on a show on a show on TLC and I forgot the name of it
Do you guys forgive me remember this there's a show with all these like they're such a christian
Hope that fucking cat comes recovers
The cat will be fine. The cat will be fine. Chris. Chris. The cat's fine.
Fuck that shit. Fuck it. Pay attention when you're driving your guy to use your house
You understand that's my woman
Hey man, you don't have to fucking go back on it.
Yeah, I already got a man to tell me what to do.
I don't need you with your fucking Fred Durst looking ass.
Well, it sounds like you're really upset about it.
It sounds like you're really over here talking to the side of the fucking idiot.
Hey, Chris, come here.
Quick, man.
Quick, quick.
Hey, yo, dude.
What am I supposed to do, Paul?
What are you doing?
The cat is fine.
See, he's not injured.
He's sore.
He's inside, doped up, resting.
Listen.
Hey, go down to the fuckers glasses.
Can you fucking not see what he's writing?
Hey, tough guy.
The Fred Dursk guy.
Hey, hey, Fred Dursk.
Hey, yeah, hey.
Fuck you.
Tough guy.
Hey, where are you at?
You anywhere near Richmond, Virginia right now?
No.
Anywhere near California side.
New Bernou.
No fighting guys, you're not allowed to pull up on each other
I'm just saying this morning didn't get it because she keeps arguing. It's wrong be quiet
I'm quiet right now
Exactly people out cuz somebody like me is gonna come up here somebody like me's gonna come up here and be like alright
Fuck it. Let's do it
It's gonna be around your neighbor, I know how he is, it's okay but it's not okay Chris
because that's my woman, I already gave her the speech, you don't have to give her the
speech again.
He's not giving me the speech, he's being a fucking dickhead.
Just stop dude.
I'm not trying to manning anybody. Does that make sense when women do that? It fucking makes it worse stop
It's fine Chris knows now I've already given you that speech. I don't regret anything I said dude if you can't fucking
I know that
Dude, I asked for the same
Shut the fuck up Chris don't do that man. I already fucking yell at her about it. It's fine. It's fine
Be quiet
No, nobody needs to yell at me.
Oh, guys, guys, guys, guys, does anybody, guys,
who knows who Corn Dog is?
Corn Dog, can you just wave so I know you're a real person?
Just wave me?
Okay, here's a real person.
Hold on one second.
I just need to put the, I'll be there.
Damn.
Hello.
Hi, psych.
Hi, how are you good? Hey everybody? I already like it. I heard that this was the cat abuse stream. Is that true?
Okay, so are you are you are you Aldi in a wig? I'm not sure that Aldi a wig guys easy all the puller
You and I was I was serious. I was serious. You don't you're not Aldi in a way. Okay, you're a different person. Okay
Are you unimpactual? Are you unimpactual jokers? Are you are you the guy with his name?
No, I'm not the real person, yes.
No, his name's not, his name's not, not Mer. Who's the guy with practical jokers? Like, like, you know, the...
No, it's a real person.
Okay, okay.
Thanks, thank you. Just, just start hurling insults as soon as I come up with it.
No, no, he's a good, they're a good-looking actor. He's a good-looking guy.
Sal has been a Sal on a, on a, Sal on a...
Yeah, Sal.
Unprobable jokers.
practical have you heard of that still have you heard me hear you heard that
person okay that that's that I watched that show anytime I'm in a hotel I just
leave it to me too you too and below deck I only watched that in a hotel okay
we're good Bernice say yeah what about chain that he has on
It's just that's not offensive, but Chris I understand where you're coming from and also I understand
It was an accident and you took the cat right to the vet and that's really what you're supposed to do in that situation, right?
Yeah, I think the cat is fine. It's really it and you know what? No, no you say before anything else
It's really my own fucking business
Well, no, it's everyone's business if you
Hey
No, you're not gonna want me over
Look if you want Chris is gonna be a cat foster, you know for rescue animals very soon, so that's his
Yeah, I used to do that
Well, yeah until you started running them all over I know right
I let the chicken get I let the
chicken get eaten by the coyotes
last week. I'm just a dumb woman
with a small brain. Yeah, at
least you know, at least you
admit it. At least admit it. I
know I need I that's why that's
why I had to get myself a man
because I can't do anything by
myself.
I don't know. Look at me. I'm
What do you call it? Okay
He's my friend
Portia
Okay, guys. Can we not
Guys, can we not keep can we not giggle that chicken on guy guy guy guys. He's getting old. We're trying to have a conversation
Stop talking about chicken. Okay. Okay, so guys
Yeah, I want to talk to I want to talk to corn corn corn dog. I'm sorry. I can't do corn dog
Have you have you been on my show before you're familiar? You are familiar. Yeah, I talked to you before it was just okay
Okay, it's just you and me
It was before you started to blow up psych. Oh my god. I was there before you
I blew up, I blew up, I blew up and then I then I just exploded so
Chris K comes, Chris K seems to come after people blow up, it's kind of weird
You saw Minnie flash the gash on, yeah I've seen the gash about a thousand times
My text message on my phone, my discord
I got on YouTube if you haven't seen Minnie's gash
Yeah, well if you guys I can't send it. I was too explicit, but just to just imagine just to just imagine a infinite
Clam, okay, hold on a second
Yeah, fucking corn dog is it's not but a fucking stomach. I mean this funny look look at him
I mean, you know what it's ugly, you know, but you know, but that look yourself
He has to really you know put on a fucking hat and really has to you know
And that's a muscle shirt, but guess what bitch? You don't even have any fucking muscles on me, dude
You're not missing none of these fucking women on here
Now that I mean you have these women what one of you have been talking your fucking ass, you know inside and out
That's what the fuck they obviously want to do. I mean to you. So guess what and get and you talk all this
You know shit about me don't you know channels, you know shit. Guess what? But now I'm here now
But now here's how me the thing though, but now you know you got my fucking attention on me bitch boy
Okay, well, I was trying to I was trying to get a word edge way. I mean I was gonna say, you know, you know
I don't know well guys if you guys if you guys annoy me again, I will bring burdo back up. Okay, burdo
You're the one that like had an accent with your cat, right? Correct. Yes
Can we can we all have a moment? Can we pray for the cat? No
No, we're supposed to talk about the cat that was a prayer for the cat
Thank you Chris. Thank you Chris.
Thank you Chris.
I appreciate that.
Birdo you ruined the moment. Birdo stop it.
The guy with the mall at two, man, like that's a big deal.
He's, he's good.
The cat's okay.
He's got some, he's, he's, he's got a little sore.
The cat's not dead.
I set him, I set him up in a room by himself
and I made him little steps up to the litter box.
So he doesn't have to hurt himself to jump in and out.
Got him food, water, comfortable bed options right now.
Yeah, my woman does, she's comforting, bro.
Hey, he's going to be able to take care of me, you know
Leif Erickson
Leif Erick
I named him after the person that discovered america
Was it Leif was it Leif Erickson or Leif Erickson? Who's who's he's a
He was the viking died
He was a singer. He was he was well everybody dies eventually. Yeah, no, he's still alive. I think let me see
You heard of the original
Okay, not okay, not to send me start throw up. Okay. Yeah, okay. No, no, no
I mean, can you guys give me like let me let's have a little like a deal here. All right
And listen a Jenny better fucking
I know
I I yeah, and I don't know if she laughed about it, but I think she was like, you know, sometimes we laugh in tragedy
Guys, have you ever done that?
It's funny, I mean Charlie what I mean what great dictator
I would never do that dude. I fucking pay attention when I drive my fucking car, especially in my fucking
Dude, I don't know how to tell you I was fucking
The fucking sun was
Right
Yeah, you better fucking hope that fucking cat comes through Doug type shit
I don't want to hear is that a self-threatening self-threatening Jansley, I mean, please
Yeah
No one's running anybody over but let's not let's not make threats on my show. I asked you several times
So please stop making threats. So
Guys the cat is fine. I think she ran over the cat's tail or something the cat's fine. Okay
Yeah, they did x-rays nothing was even broken
And that's a tiny cat, so it's
With cats so much because they have those weird bones where they could fall from buildings in their find you worry about internal bleeding
Yeah, I know, I know that's why I took the cat to the vet, that's why I took the cat to the vet, that's why I took the cat to the vet, that's why I took the cat to the vet, that's why I took the cat to the vet, that's why I took the cat to the vet, that's why I took the cat to the vet, that's why I took the cat to the vet, that's why I took the cat to the vet, that's why I took the cat to the vet, that's why I took the cat to the vet, that's why I took the cat to the vet, that's why I took the cat to the vet, that's why I took the cat to the vet, that's why I took the cat to the vet, that's why I took the cat to the vet, that's why I took the cat to the vet, that's why I took the cat to the vet, that's why I took the cat to the vet, that's why I took the cat
I'm not joking about it. I am not joking about it. I am not joking about it. I am not joking about it. I am not joking about it. I am not joking about it. I am not joking about it. I am not joking about it. I am not joking about it. I am not joking about it. I am not joking about it. I am not joking about it. I am not joking about it. I am not joking about it. I am not joking about it. I am not joking about it. I am not joking about it. I am not joking about it. I am not joking about it. I am not joking about it. I am not joking about it. I am not joking about it. I am not joking about it. I am not joking about it. I am not joking about it. I am not joking about it. I am not joking about it. I am not joking about it. I am not joking about it. I am not joking about it. I am not joking about it. I am not joking about it
Chris the Chris is okay. Okay, it's fine
Right now to make sure it's okay
Hey
That's my that's my woman you have to time him out first
on her a bitch right now, I don't have to but yeah, it's working. But I will add like, you know,
there we go. He's like, he left. What's going on with Chris? What happened? Why? What's going
with Chris? Uh, he's like, he's one little, he's having a little hard night tonight. He's like,
he's like a little bit emotional about things that are really none of his business. And like,
you know, he's asking you something. Do you know, do you know who Chuck Stagall is?
uh
Well, he was streaming one night and his cat got hit by a car
And everyone was like we'll pay for you
To take the cat to the vet and he refused. He said the cat's fine
He showed the cat on camera and the cat was bleeding from the mother's
Oh, it was like in town. Oh shit rest in peace fluffy. So how about
Yeah, you know what if we see the cat, you know, you know, you know, we always want to we always want to keep a keep an eye
Keep an eye on the she took it. She took it to the better an area
And yeah, I was gonna I was gonna say like that happened to like a Lisa last year
Like something happened with her dog like one time her dog. I think her dog
Here's a full screen here. Oh
There's the dog's cat spy the cat's fine. Okay. Both screeners like there we go. Thank you
Why is she doing that? Oh my god. Where is she? Oh my god. Oh, she's a lot. Oh, she's fine
Yeah, they gave him a
He looks fine
what's his name?
oh no no no no no
it's not
they didn't shave, they didn't shave anywhere or anything
the cat is one of the most expensive
I know what's going on
I still like to draw a little
okay
Look at him, he's got multiple bed options, you know, there's some heat, you know, there's
his little litter box set up with makeshift stairs, food, water, he's fine.
Okay, chocolate thunder you you go you go you you oh you care about cats more and
And you're better tarot than me. Okay. Okay. Well, I love names. I love names and yeah
That's my favorite
All right guys, but my battery is like dangerously. So I'm gonna hop down here and put in case we do you have a lovely
Bye bye Chris. Bye everybody else. Just look all around you when you're in the driveway next time
Yeah, that's true. Yeah. No, I wanted her. I wanted her. You're right. You're right. See you later. Have a great night. All right.
Okay, didn't have to reiterate that. Talk to you later, honey. Thank you. You too, honey. Oh, not me. Yeah.
Um, no, he left he left in a huff. He like he was superior because he was called out for calling someone a bitch
But I love Chris, you know
He's just going a little nuts with nuts over Christine
I mean come on this is like he's a cool dude. I love Chris, but like he gets shitty with women
And I don't know what's up
No, I've never had a personal issue with Chris at all ever but then
Man, it's almost like he's like
Sexist I think
What is a three-card draw brother sure?
Of course, of course, is there what is there more than a three-card draw?
Yeah, you can do the you can read out the whole deck if you wanted to
Yeah
It's a good
Yeah, and tarot is
Tarot is kind of like poker for women a little bit, but I don't men can enjoy it to you. Okay. He is the magic
Three is the magic number. Okay. Yeah, three
I think magic
three
So one, okay, I got it. Okay, one, two,
Oh God, can I, can you do mine after him? Yeah
Oh God, I'm gonna get such a bad thing
So we have, okay, so we have this, okay.
So we have for you this three of pentacles.
Okay, so this could be that you're working on something
and then, you know, I like to think of it as like, you know,
you're like, you're advancing in your craft
or whatever, or, you know, your abilities
and then you're really improving
and you've got people like taking notice in you.
Maybe these people went, met with a work with you.
They're like, oh, yeah, well, he's,
hey, he's doing a little better than we thought, you know,
he's figuring things out.
Okay.
so that's the uh three apanicals okay then we have this eight of wands so this is kind of
in the present position and so this is like some kind of some kind of news is coming in really fast
so it might be in regard to this uh three apanicals uh person that wants to maybe work with you
you can see this guy right here he's wearing an apron right and he's like he's like i think he's
And so in just eight of wands, this is like, this is like a little lot of fast activity, fast, fast, uh,
Okay, it's working really fast, moving fast. Yeah
But then we have okay, but also be aware because we have the pages sorts and pages or I call this like the spy card
And so somebody is watching somebody's they're watching
Yeah, every move it's a warning. Okay, so
You're welcome you're welcome
Yeah, you're ready for yours, okay
You don't need like my birthday or something. No, I don't need your birthday. I don't need your birthday. Oh, I thought that's how that work
You let you let the cards. Yeah, how do you start a cool cards? I started off. I just
Oh
No, I mean, it's like, you know, you can and sometimes people can say oh they can look at the astrological sign
I'll correspond oftentimes. Oh, you know to it's like a really cool
I'll tell you that burger. Yeah. Oh, you're a burger. Okay. Yeah. Okay. Okay. That's good. I'll let you know your burger. Okay
uh earth sign you know um we have yeah right adhd they have uh or ocd they uh they are
very good at organizing but they're sometimes not very good at um being subtle bit okay they're
not really virgins okay they're not really virgins okay not virgins but go
Yeah, okay. I know I know but that's what it comes from the virgin
Okay, so so okay, so so for you I have the wheel of fortune, okay
So we have the wheel of fortune card, you know the wheel of fortune is you know
It's always it's always the wheel of fortune always spinning. It says actually TRO on it
You know it has it has the whole tarot wheel on there and the whole ass the diacal wheel on
Yeah, some Hebrew, yeah, there's Hebrew letters on this, and you'll find a lot of, you'll find a lot of you guys, yeah, well, yeah.
Okay, well, let's let's not get in politics right now. But okay, so we do have we do have what looks appears to be like
Wait, here's like Ezekiel or see Ezekiel's wheel like there's like these wheels within wheels
Remember there's wheels within a wheel and they had the animals
Animals behind them the guarding and say that all these poor elements with America. Okay, so it looks like things are going in your favor
At the moment, okay, but okay, then you got this right here
Yeah, you get the seven you get the seven is you have the seven of swords and reverse and so who's this like person like trying to like
You know, it's not working. Whatever. They try it's upside down. It's upside down. So it was upset. Yeah, it came upset down
and so this is you know, you
Yeah, usually it's like a six if it was upright if it was upright of you like there's a person like stealing from you
We're trying to see from there. Yeah, okay. It's upside down
But if it's upside down, I say that means it's probably like
It's either been exposed or didn't work or, you know, they tried something because you are really protecting what you have right there.
You also have your money on your mind and there's more circles within circles.
You're like in the center of the field.
Oh, the way you move the card, yeah, I see the circles.
Yeah, you can see the circles again, and you see also got the speed on speed on there, too
Okay, so you're really like it's ability. Maybe that's why this air because air always has all these ideas of how they're gonna steal the money
You know, unless it's like, you know, be out curtsy. It's usually doesn't use doesn't work. Well, it's like because you know
If air signs like an air sign you mean
If an air like a money type guy
Right, no, but it's like when I'm saying gem like a Gemini or an air sign would rule more in
Being able to pull money out of thin air right especially in Gemini which rules of fiat currency
Which is like, you know the money the money that's printed out
See of life. I guess otherwise otherwise
And otherwise you can see the the earth sign is a pentacle, which is a coin. It's like it actually is
Yeah, I'll put him back here next page
He reminds me I feel like I'm I feel like I'm on a movie set. I feel like I'm on a movie set. I've got it
Is that is that Aldi is that Aldi in a wig and a must pick mustache? I seriously use you just had to watch it
You know what Aldi looks just like Aldi fuck now. He doesn't look like Aldi. He looks like he looks to me
Everyone's everyone's everyone's blending together for me now at this point, you know, it's like everyone
There he goes, that's what he looks like he looks at miss potato head
All the brainless fries. Okay. Oh, oh who left who left? Oh, and we get the dog up bangar. We had the dog up
Okay, horn who left? Oh
Page okay, it's okay. Sorry mate. Don't need to take the piss out of you
Don't I'm sorry, if you if you'd like to have an adult calm
It's not burdo. It's paid as mispays
I know I'm talking to burdo and chat who tried Oh, okay. I'm sorry. I'm sorry
If you want to have a calm adult back and forth where we can hash out whatever issues we have with each other
Yeah, I'd love to do that. That's
They're not they're not they're not you don't want to have a conversation with him because it looks like he's in the trailer part
No, it's okay. You know, it's good. It's not it's good to like talk to burdo. Okay. Okay, whatever
It's easy. Let me talk. So it's good to talk to burdo in the chat because they can't type as fast as they can
Talk as though you will never you'll they they have never for one second and like the probably 20 minutes
I've had them on my panel ever stopped one second to ever stop talking or here so they're purely a
So so our weapon
Yeah, it's like a sonar weapon or some kind of yeah, yeah
Metaphors like that's a yeah
Page is actually pretty fucking quick with that kind of stuff though. I will give her that
Page has page II I'm alright my fucking Mike wasn't working for like the whole time and so I was just talking to nobody
Nobody's in the chat so you're talking to nobody in the chat. Oh wonderful so great
Yes, you can use you look like you. I can't find my zero cards, but you have you know, you know, you can you can even use you know
You know, you can they have randomly generated tarot card
But they have tarot cards and fucking like a trailer park
Yeah, okay, Ziggy Ziggy Ziggy Ziggy you're about you're about to have annoyed me
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, man. Oh, I just didn't see you
I mean, I'm in a night. I'm in a nice. I'm in my studio rain. It's nice Ziggy. Ziggy. He looks like a young George Lucas
Give the fucking guy a break. I mean, it's like
I'm giving him a break my bad
I'm saying he lives in a trailer park. I would be lucky to have a trailer if I wish I wish I had a trailer
I want a trailer I want one I want one
I want the best one. I want the best trailer. I went
It is but I wouldn't mind living in like a like a really nice trailer
Came up to ask what is your issues with trailers?
And I said I don't have one. I would live in one.
I would live in one.
It's much more on sound days that look way nicer than some of the fucking places you clowns live in.
So what are your all issues with trailers?
I
Was out of line right there. I'm sorry dude. No, no Ziggy Ziggy give us a house tour. Come on. Let's do it
Let's have it. I'm outside by the fire pit. I mean, I got a nice place. I don't know what you guys are talking about
But your Christmas
I do
So you're absolutely right right now right now. It is a summer solstice. It's a summer solstice tree right now. No, that's not
Don it's a Donnie Darko. Donnie Darko like you seem like a very nice cool smart person
It's a Donna. I do have shade my shades are up guys if you ever go home with woman if she has a Christmas tree
Oh my gosh, no
It's always green for st. Patrick's day and then it's like it's the summer solstice. There's a white some white lights on it and then it's very
No, uh, but Thanksgiving we'll have it if you need a care bear dog you corn dogs got you. So don't worry about it ladies
Just a sweetheart
Bader? No, Bader was not in the chat. It was actually just Berto and Chris K was kind of just like, oh yeah, Jan was here and then yeah.
Yeah, I'm a woman. I love my woman.
Hi Paige, how you doing, Booda Poe?
I love my woman.
I'm good summer, how are you?
I'm doing good. I just can't believe guys talk silly about trailers.
That's right. Yeah, okay. I'll tell you sweepy if you want to know
Yeah, sweepy. That's from a checker's guide to the universe. That's right. The secret of life, right? Yeah
This is actually the aspect ratio of a VHS tape, but it's also what they call chance, right 43. Mm-hmm
Yeah, I would probably
See that's why I but I see if you do like I look like bone clicks. I look like Aldi. I look like everybody
Gustavo, hey, thank you everybody. Yes. Did you see did you see and this is just true crimes?
It's not politics. Did you see that the guy from the Idaho forp just pled guilty?
Yeah, he plead guilty. Yeah, they took the distance it's off. He pled guilty to every single charge. Hold on. Listen
He took the debt that they took the distances off
He'll spend the rest of his life in prison with no chance of parole and he did plead guilty to every charge
No way
Just happened
Okay, well, you know
Every day and I haven't heard her say that yet
Reminds me of like, you know
John Wayne, Casey, John Wayne, Casey, John Wayne, Casey. No, no, no for the
Oh, I don't know no for the out of her for that. I don't know guys guy guy. I don't know is this the case that I know is this is not the
It's not that Kansas. Yeah, I don't know anything about
It's the college students remember the four college students about two years ago my year and a half two years ago
They the guy went in their house and
And I laughed all of them. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that I think that's a psyop
I've watched that that appears to be a psychological operation to me
It looks like there's a lot of a lot of the numerologies in there even his name
Is it Rothsburg or some Rothsburg or something? No, it's Brian. It starts with a K. I forget it's last night
Okay, I think it's not politics. It's true crime. No, that wasn't me
Yeah, I'm not talking politics at all. This is that's nothing to do with politics at all
Yeah, and we don't have to talk about it. I just didn't know if anybody heard about it. That's all my bad. Sorry
I'm back to being region idiots. What the fuck you fucking morons. Is that better?
Yes
Yeah
Yes, well, yeah, the Cyclops was also you know psych Cyclops and then we have op it also have a goddess named ops and then that was also
you know
No, they're my mom was all about that shit man
I send me links every day and that's what I meant to that girl
Yeah, it was it was burger. It was it was burger. Yeah, yeah
No, I mean it was I get it though. Thank you. It was a pretty crazy. It was a crazy case. I mean it is a crazy case
Well, I suppose you're quick, but he actually actually played fucking guilty
When every
Come on, it's crazy when shit goes down like that. We've all got guns. We're gonna kill you motherfuckers
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, I don't think so. I think that was
That I was just kidding. I didn't see what he said
I get it everybody each community has their own thing I get it
Yeah
Broke is what I'm saying is when everybody has guns no matter
Like the guy in the killing
Yeah, okay, but yeah, you're not supposed to show guns. I don't want to say that say the word too too often
So let's not talk about murders or anything
Yeah, it's interesting. Okay good thing he's like guilty you said or like you know
Yeah, he's like guilty to all of his charges
They took this and the soft the table and he's gonna spend less life in prison without parole
Well, he's now now he's now he's the worst safe guy because you know what I think is the biggest sigh up
I've I saw recently was this Gabby Petito case
that case, where it was just like, so weird.
What do you mean?
Yes, I knew that case.
I covered that.
I covered that case. What do you mean by spy op because that was a
Yeah, we're looking at look at first. Well, look at first of all look at the pictures that were released
There's a picture of her with a monarch butterfly monarch butterflies
Or of course like a big symbol of the MK ultra and like a little sign
There's pictures of her butterfly wings and there's a
Yeah, yeah, it could be could be but she it was just like no she there's just big this big one painted behind her very very elaborate
But anyway, also her boyfriend's name
Brian Landry, so that kind of sounds like brain laundry like brainwashing. It sounds so it's kind of like they'll do like little things like
No, you're saying it's not hold on one second psyche slow down. I'm trying to understand what you're saying so
you're saying that it's like not real it was just stage or something or yeah so it was it was a
stage it was a stage and remember what they did remember all they found were bones like a month
or two later all they found were bones right it's like a month or two later that there were just
all bones and and then he was he's unalive it's always like they always unalive everybody so
there's nobody to like say anything else everything's on everything's very did he stretch
Taiki or Celtic if you study like Brian Landry brain laundry, like it's like brainwashing, right?
When you look at something then you say that it's a scythe right because I look at that case and I see very real case
I see two very real people. I see two very young people that have a very typical domestic violence situation
And it's sad very sad
Um, but so when you look at something, how do you distinguish between say one case from the next to be like, okay?
Well, that's a sigh up case. So that's you know, not really real, but this case is I basically say
You should probably question everything that's being presented to you by the mainstream media because if they're like putting out people's names
And so these are like people this is these are like all approved processes to put people's names out or just gonna create
Create a storyline don't you mean
don't you mean the mainstream police law enforcement well they're not supposed to share
they're not supposed to share all this information that they were shared with about these cases
you know no i i i agree with her i i don't like whenever somebody's like okay that happened on
july 7th yeah because it kind of takes away and i'm sorry to get me to catch you up but like
The lady at the lady that I was a neighbor fucking Brianna Taylor
You know I was her neighbor and stuff like that
Me and you've kind of talked about that a little bit and I remember when people would be like oh
That's such a side-off, but I'm like wait a minute. I was there that night. I heard what the police did
I've seen the aftermath of every single thing. You know what I mean?
Like I've seen you know, and so it's hard for me when people even with this Gabby case
I did I covered it on my channel and we deep-dived and it did everything like that and it was
Very and when I say typical, I don't mean like I mean it was a bad domestic violent case
But it's something that a lot of people deal with you know, and it could happen to anybody like that
To sit there and because it's like well, you're saying that these people that you know and their family suffered
It's not real that you okay if you're doing if you're doing on your channel
Are you not pissed off when people are like, yeah that happened on this date at that time?
at this yeah and that's why i'm gonna i'm gonna have just a regular
station i believe in the analogy and strong say
then they'll say and that means six six six if you add it all down
like that's stupid to me man no no no one says i just don't understand it and that's why i like
i'm not i don't want to argue with psyche or anything like that no i see these cases at all
and i'll i'll i'll summer let me just say like if so think about how tightly like the information
is kind of controlled in this country like you know like if something's gonna be put like like
words are gonna be said in the news like you know last people people's last names so these names
News is saying these, there's shows making whole programs
and series about these cases and things like that.
Like, you know, and so like a lot of them
are just tied in with Disney.
You guys, you'll see so much.
product placement you'll see Nike you'll see sports teams you'll see
they're always wearing so suspicious hat they're wearing Tiffany blue they're wearing
living and there's so many there's and there's no number 33 everywhere or 333 or there's number
93 I mean there's like a lot of code numbers and things like that I mean if you're like buddy if
you notice them it's kind of like pointing out oh there's something there
That just kind of tells me this don't take it too seriously.
It's like, you know, we have real lives
and the real things will happen in our lives.
That's what we state seriously.
We should like look at kind of what we learned about on TV
as kind of like entertainment or stories.
Yeah, but let me add, when you made somebody that was...
I've never seen that in heavy metal.
Ever when you meet somebody that maybe is attached to these cases or it was there when this things happened or whatever
And then they tell you like no I get that's how you see it
But like I really lived there like I really seen this I really you know, whatever and then when people still try to argue
You know, it's just
I'm not saying it's every case but yeah, but I'm but even if we just go beyond like okay psychological operation
I could planned out operation
I say still, there's like things come in synchronicities
and things will happen at certain auspicious times
or in auspicious times.
Astrology, numerology might have things to do with it
and just like, you know, how everything is connected
and so, you know, there's more to it.
There's like, you know, there can be that aspect to it too.
But I think that just like a lot of like the world is a stage like like a lot of the stuff that's presented to us is like, you know, the powers that say, yeah,
That's a that I mean, you know, that's a quote, right? The world is yes, it's in Shakespeare.
I agree. You should question everything, right? I have no issue with that. But like what there's real people and there's real
Life's that are effective and you know, I mean, it's just hard for me to be like, well, you know, that's a good, you know, whatever even
when everybody calls certain things conspiracy things and I'm like well that's not
certainly you know that's how you see it but I see it as real life like you know what I mean
so I don't know it's just I guess it's a perspective how people look but I just that's
another that's another I don't get that they'll have some of these cases will be just so
overly the top you know just like horrible so many horrible things would have happened
them and they're so emotional and so unspeakable and so like these details come out where it was
Question that because it's like if you because then it's like oh you're bending so it's like so it's kind of really easy
If you get people in their emotions, and they don't think kind of rationally that they're there
It'll jump on whatever cause you're kind of kind of trying to guide them towards you use the right, you know
Remember guys remember
Happens right
Right in some happens and it's like, you know, I think there's there's like there's a chance
There's chance in the world. There's there's you know, things that are fated
There's things that just happened the right time right place the right time. There's all kinds of stuff
You know, everything's everything. Well, that's what this woman came up and she was like, you know
What do you have against mental homes? I don't because I grew up in one, but here's what I was meaning
This is what she didn't get
because she doesn't know me and that's fair when I was growing up in the
mobile home man it was fucking fist fights every fucking day all the time
my mom I mean yes I mean you know yeah yeah I know I know that I know but
that's how I grew up you see when I get it I mean yeah a mobile home with
All right, that's gonna be fist fights and fucking bitching and you know, whatever and yeah
What I mean, it's not like the world is not the world is not king of the hill
I mean, maybe it maybe it's like a little less charming than that TV show
I mean, but it's like, you know, it's like, yeah, we can I can go sit and drink beers out
Wait, it's like don't you have to like put people down for living in a trailer park. I mean come on
No, no, no, no, no, no like she was saying though
She was looking at it, you know, and no no wait, hold on. She was looking at it in a nice light
I'm looking well. I really just came up to be silly. I would I'm saying I was just me and I would I would have a fucking
I'd sell all my shit right now dude to have a little mumble home. I would oh
You should get a little tiny home if I had to like get disappear
I would just like it I'd buy a little tiny home, you know, I can buy it on Amazon if you can either prefab to like
10 grand you can have a little house put down in the middle of nowhere
I just have like, you know, I'd make sure that there was like water electricity and
Yeah
Yeah, I have everything like, you know airdrop. Yeah, but that's what but that's what I was saying against her
I was like, no, that's no that shit and thinking just so you know, I just really came
I mean I was being serious, but I was being silly too and by the way this lady her name's summer and how are you doing z?
I'm nice to meet you. Nice to meet you, too
Yeah, yeah when I'm on bullshit, you'll know because I'll be like great screaming and stupid
But I'm just I was really just being kind of silly. I mean, but I wasn't being silly, you know
I think I'm an asshole
Get ready dude if you fucking like me then fucking people will be like
Okay, I am an asshole sometimes though, so it's okay
Listen, hey shut the fuck up. I have an instant to show some respect
No one gives a fuck what you're talking about and you're fucked you and your instant. How about that?
No, this is this is for the cat. This is for the cat that got ran over, bro
She's gone, she's not here to talk about we're not talking about the cat
What do you mean, I don't forget fucking that bitch
Okay, okay, what it's not it's not frickin
911 I mean Jesus is it somebody else's cat. It's not even here the cat's fine. We all saw we all saw the cat
You won't shut up about the foot the cat
No, there really is a cat. I didn't know. I thought he was being silly.
No, I'm bad. I thought he was just being normal and all.
Jan just nicked the cat with her claws. The cat's fine.
It's been to the vet. It's been to the vet. The cat looks fine.
Well, my kitty says, perfect. Good energy to your kitty.
I don't know why she fucking put it on camera, but okay.
Sweepies like no, I mean I have the attitude where it's like, you know, I love cats so much
But it's like she feels like she has to prove shit to people man, and I hate that
She didn't mean to do it. It's like she's not only long as she tried it was an accident
You know you had an accident Chris you never done an accident something on accident
Listen to some of us our kitties are our babies, so if your wife your old lady is you know like a normal chick, then yeah
That's our baby
Listen, I already gave her the speech Chris K came up and gave her an extra speech at the whole Chris K to be quiet about it
He didn't be quiet about a lady. That's Dan
What's the cat can we I mean I'm trying to get survive fucking all right now dude come on
Oh, well sweetie if that was your kitty
I was just talking shit to Chris cuz we always talk shit to each other like so don't take it yeah
You know I was literally just fucking around like
Chris is fucked up and he saw that fucking he would say and I'm outspoken to
He thought that he would tell the girl to, you know, fuck you.
Summer, Summer, Summer, but he goes to the level where he's like...
He's like, oh, I'm gonna come you know run you run you down with my
Man like he like on my side man. He's a fucking good dude. I know but why why why are you why are you threatening women on my
Yeah, well on my show
He didn't know he was drinking and he didn't
Shit well, so do I but I mean I don't I don't I don't threaten
I don't I don't I don't say I don't think it seems like that like oh
And it's fine
Psych it wasn't threats it was fucking telling people to fucking pay attention when they drive
Is it they're why no, I know we know it's like everyone everyone kind of knows
I already told her
The best thing I could tell you is don't take shit around here serious. Please, please don't eat
Already told her. Oh
You didn't catch that and that's fine, man. It's all right
Oh
We all love cats and it's terrible, but I don't I'm not gonna sit here in like fine
And it's good to get emotionally. I have to say like emotionally like you know a little bit
I don't even understand how you guys like cats like I'm I'm a dog person. There's cats are amazing
Yeah, don't you like don't you like to cuddle up with a warm pussy warm pussy?
No, I like dogs, man. I fucking love dogs
Everyone loves pussy everyone loves pussy like I'll throw a cat. I just showed Margie
What would you do you did what?
I
Everyone's showing their pussy. I don't want to see your
Your cat
I would like to say this has been interesting, but it's not even educational
Well, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's
He wasn't educated though. You do I hope I hope he was entertained if he wasn't educated, but I think if you
Yeah, I think he's like, you know, maybe maybe he's a little bit insane and you know, yeah, your things I
The other night, no, no, no a vanguard. Oh, this dude Chris is insane
I mean the band the British guy the British the British guy. He was just you know
He just said the show was not education at all.
No, Chris has been insane, no, he's just really good.
No, no, Chris, I know I'm saying Vanguard's insane.
Chris is just a little bit...
a little bit
The screws a little bit loose the screws a little bit loose, but it can be screwed back in yeah, but you know
We all have a screw screws, you know, I certainly do okay, so no no shade no shade. That's what that's what fucking screwdrivers are for
Yeah, we're all crazy. That's why we're here
Who's working the screwdriver because I don't see that
Hopefully not you. Hopefully not you or I'll be getting a little
Having a little bottom me. No, no, no, no, no. No, let me say no
All of us in the chat and on the panel have to be a little root root because we're all here every day
They're metaphorical there's
For me, I don't know
Oh drinking bar is the bar this is a my show is not a bar my show is not a bar for you get out of here
It's not cheers. Go go watch tears on TV. Get out of here the hang out. Yeah
Nobody knows your name
Okay, I kick them out. Oh, okay. I'll let I'll make it. I just want to sit outside and appreciate this not some yeah
That's a bar. I can kick your ass know the curve. You can set it
You can sit on the front of the bar. How about that? It's a bar a page. Yes pages here
Miss page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page page
Oh, you want to come back in the bar, sir?
I thought I'd ask you to leave, sir.
Proxy later, back.
Not by summer, I love you.
Ziggy, what are you doing?
You're trying to come back inside the bar?
Even the bouncer kicked through you out,
because you annoyed the owner again.
What's yours, I think.
Oh, that was a good one.
That was a good one.
It is.
It's not cheers.
It's not Mr. Good Bards.
It's a.
It's a bad bad bar. It's a very good. It's a very good friend. We don't serve alcohol. We don't serve alcohol. I mean, to me, it's a bar. The only good bars are open bars or else it's like BYOB. That's more of a, you know, you're a guest in my house. Yeah, it is. That's exactly what it is. BYOB. Right.
I'm just saying in general. I'm just saying in general we were so interested in other people and other people's shadows other people are doing
Something wrong other people are not saying anything specific. I'm just saying in general
That's what human human nature is like we want to go chase after everybody else's shadows
We all have our own shadow
Yeah, may I say something?
Yes, Chris Chris was inserting himself into something that I had already talked about and he didn't know that and then fucking no
We're okay, man. Okay. Okay. I
Don't know. I don't know. I don't have things get so close. He does keep talking about it. So Chris
Come down. Oh
Just like, you know poor cat
I know oh
You know about it. We all we all yeah, that's on to bater. Yeah. Yeah, we all
Yeah, we all love cats
Still won't come up on the fucking chat on your panel. You want to chase after Christine shadow?
I know I want to chase after Christine shadow too because I mean it's like some people's shadows that are pretty annoying and it's like
But it's like a short of like taking off people's heads. We got a like we got a you know
Just let people like learn the lessons for themselves. Oh, I love you too. Spunky. How are you?
Dude, I would have a dog where I live
I don't have like any yard so like I would have to like walk my dog and shit like that
But yeah, I'm too man, bro Chris. I have to man. I love my dogs, dude
Yeah, I would you know what kind of dog you have what kind of bro breed rods to rocks no Christine Christine
What do you say guys?
See and everything. Yeah, man. They're I mean there's so many good breeds of dogs like fucking I had I had like a
Fucking a chow. I had a fuck yeah
Those are cool
Yeah, so I mean, did they have a big blood they have a big black tongue that I would kiss you with yes
okay, and
I know they do
These dogs bro. We're fucking Houdini bro
Like they would get out of the yard that I had they would dig holes and fucking go like kill all the neighborhood dogs
Like kill them literally no no no please please don't please don't tell your story. I don't I don't I don't want to hear this story
I don't
No, you know
People's animals being on a lot. I just don't know what like a large scale. I don't like that
I'm not trying to you know, I'm just I'm just saying what happens. Okay. I know right, but who know who asked nobody asked
How many how many my mind? No, I did no I asked him
He said how many animals has have your have your have your every people's pets
Yeah, I have a raw wallers man, and they
perform around the perimeter
Yeah, but your dog your dogs aren't meant to like this guard your chickens your dogs are meant to be members of your family
Big you loved, you know, they're not for people
My family, okay, they're gonna guard his family for sure
Hell yeah
Break the door down. They're gonna slide. He's gonna get him
Well, I say, you know, I say, you know
Have the cat's night. Yeah, the dogs should be protecting the house, too
They know I'll give you I'll be one example man. Um, I couldn't have a male
I couldn't have a mailbox anymore, dude. I had the
transfer it to the post office because they were
Like this guy, you know, well, I mean they're probably attacking the
I'm trying to buy my time here
Is that all I get to see it like a trouble
It's a fucking person that was they were like oh get him
I wasn't saying get them. No, no. No, they were just like, what the fuck is this?
Well, okay. Well, that's why I got you guys tampering with mail is a federal offense. You will get federal prison time
We're talking about dogs. We're talking about dogs. Oh, okay. Well
I had a mail box
So I mail box. Yeah. Yeah, I had a mailbox like a boxer like a boxer you're talking about or you had a mailbox
No, I'm mail. No, I'm mailbox for mail. Okay. Okay
There's a male box man the mailman would give me fucking mail
Was your male man? Is it was your male man a woman? Was your male man woman? Just an instant man. How is that possible?
It would be both, but like they would be
It's a new day and age and new day and age
It's a new day and age what you guys you should lock your mail up lock up your mail lock up your mail like you'd lock up your
You know your daughters
Mr.. Big I don't need that. I'm running around
Oh, no, I didn't say, no, I, I said, I got to have.
You too man. It looks like you what do you drive fucking out you try truck diesel truck?
No
Why do I look like I drive a diesel truck?
Like maybe like a like a trucker, you know you go down the road
It's like he drives out the little race car in his avatar and then a good times looks like he drives a tractor
I don't know. What do you think guys?
What is that? What is an attractive look like he drives?
Probably drives that limo. Oh, that's Janice Janice on
I drive a Toyota Camry. I am a district manager. Don't you ever disrespect me like that again?
Is that from the office is that from the office over doing that one guys file your
He said something about driving, you know a Chrysler or something like that and tried to use his car as a
As a flex like a flex
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, but but he was talking to his family. It's like they were sitting at the dinner table
Yeah, I'm a district manager. You will not disrespect me in such a way
District manager like what Walmart
Does it matter I
Am a district manager
That's that's that shit that the Karen's pull, you know, it's like do you know who I am? It's like nobody gives a fuck
Crazy-eyed bitch
Well
Hey, look, you know, you could say that you've never like drove in your driveway and actually ran over your cat
Okay, okay, so that's the end of that conversation. Okay, so I mean I said I didn't want to talk about her cat anymore
Let's leave her cat out of it. You know, you're poor cat the cats ears are probably burning with all the shit Chris is talking
I mean about her owner that's her that's her owner her owners took her to the vet Chris
I mean, you know fault her for
Having an accident so I was going to say there's this family called I think they're called not the duggers
I think the duggers is a different family. Well, family as they're called they have another show
There's done their show on tlc. I forgot the name but they've lived in basically in utah. I think and they're a pretty weird family
But the mother when uh, you know, they have like six or seven kids or something
The mother was uh, one of the kids was a twin
And the mother was riding her tractor around one day and she ran over one of her
One of her children and her children her child died
You know and she lives with that we she lives with that with that horrible feeling about and so you don't want to like you know
Rub that kind of feeling in okay. Let's not rub the feeling in okay
You know everyone back up here. Can we just be nice or do everyone like why is everyone like you know
I have a horrible story a horrible story. I'm just devastated nice to each other. I think I
What's my this left who just left? Oh
Chris K just left no he tears
Don't tell me story
It's kind of it's a bittersweet ending. So
Great yesterday afternoon afternoon mind you a raccoon came on my Linai, which is actually
Let me finish
Well, I've done that too so my dog which is like four pounds went
After it and I thought the raccoon bit my dog and I was devastated because there was blood around my dog's mouth
I looked and
Stop and my dog is the one who bit the raccoon
There's no bite marks. No nothing now. My dog is up to date with this rabies vaccine and everything well
I called the
The dog people or whatever because that has to be a rabbit raccoon to come out during the day
Something's not normal. Well now they want to take my dog from me
So I'm hiding my dog and told them the dog disappeared
It's like Dorothy you're like Dorothy and Wizard of Oz who's like trying to protect Toto and they're trying and like some witches trying to
The only way to check to see if it has rabies is to put it to sleep and cut its head off. Oh my god
The only way they can check for rabies in the brain, so I'm hiding my dog
Yeah, get get the dog a wig get get it get posy like a
No, it's not posy. It's my other dog. Oh, okay. You're other dog
I'm hiding it from animal control. I'm hiding a freaking dog. Is it in the attic is like and frank or is it?
Well, they can't legally come in my house
That's funny because it reminds me of the mobile home whenever we hit fucking
Yeah, the dog the dog I'm putting a dog in witness protection
Was it my dog? What the hell's wrong with these people? Your name's Christine everything
Everything I hate people
I hate people too
Gonna see Anne Frank. Yeah
Yeah, we hear you Chris. How are you Chris? I have to hide my dog. Isn't that ridiculous? I have to hide my dog
Well, I think it's stupid that you have to pay taxes on a car. They're not take. Well, I
Bet I bet you guess it's ridiculous to have to pay insurance on a car too
Uh-huh. Yeah. Can you hear me? Can you hear me? Yes, I can hear you. Sorry. We also pay for water. We also pay for water and energy, which are
available. Everything. Listen, Christine, do you own a gun? Do you own any guns? I do.
Okay, well, here's the thing, like fucking, these goddamn fucking, uh, what is it, uh,
I do. I, I, they go after my chickens and I pee-pew them.
As summer. I've done many of them. What did they call you again? Sorry, I'm fucking brain dead for a second.
Raccoons, raccoons, these raccoons, shoot them.
I do no no no no no no no no no no no no when when they go after my chickens
I have a right to protect my chickens, and I will it all cost
Oh, yeah, I don't I don't like to but why why does he insist on the time I killing stuff and like in like more like
Christine knows what to do Christine knows she has
Why do we have to why do we have to talk about we're gonna do the raccoons? We know we're gonna do the raccoons
You know, we don't have to talk about what we're gonna do the raccoons
Sweet pea, he's a Satanist. What does he do? What does he do to cats? Sweet pea tell me
He's crispy. He's his magical rituals. Can't hear these little babies
He's a KKK. Oh
He's not he is here watch his fingers watch that he gives the sign just watch them. Oh my god
So Chris so so but Chris so you're you're a wizard too, so mr. Big pipes is a wizard your wizard
Oh, God. Oh, gosh. They're big pipes as a wizard
Well, he thinks he's a part I told Saints about it. I was like
Oh, yeah, I'm a winner too. Yeah Saints way cooler than I don't I told I told saying that I was like hey
I was like and say was like hey psyche. What's up? How you like where have you been?
And he's like, oh, yeah, he's like, oh, man, Mr. Big Pies.
He's like, Mr. Big Pies is he's like, he's like, he's like,
Mr. Big Pies is not going to can't mess with like you or me.
Like, you know, he's like me, dude.
That's why I get along with fucking saying he look at Vader.
He agrees with me.
Yeah, they're pretty cool, man.
They don't talk about killing wreck.
Don't talk about killing animals.
Oh, he's he's he left.
OK, I don't.
No, no, no, you're not saying that you do it in defense of your own animals. That's what she was saying
And that's what I do
The last of the kick kick coming to your the threads near your state with yeah, I told him
I said and I said everyone had a kick at a how
You know, you were like we're like poking out his eyes on the on the stream. He's like, yeah
He's like I was doing that. He's like but he kept coming back and attacking me and stuff
Yeah, I talked to saying today a little bit
Same looks like he's doing good. I talked to Benny recently
You know like big pipes been here. I thought you ban I ban yeah, I ban I ban him off stream yard and I ban
I don't know if you know this but
psyche, I don't know if you know this but
st
lives
Pretty close to where I was growing up. Don't you don't see?
Yeah, well, thank you. You don't have to say too much more, but yeah
Yeah, I know that story. Yeah, I I've known saint for I met him on tridents chat like probably about a year ago
I would never I would I would never let a fucking raccoon fucking draw blood on my dog or my cat anything
My dog they didn't draw blood on my dog my dog do blood on that record should be in prayer
She's been out there. Why do you have fucking raccoons out in your property in the first place?
get some traps because I live you don't understand I have I have a forest preserve behind me I have
wild boars I have deers I have snakes I have alligators I have a possum I have armadillos
so I can take it. I don't mean to call you baby doll like that but literally if you have animals if
you have animals man you're going to have raccoon. Chris is it true that you are a satanist? Chris are
you a satanist or in the clan? I believe in religion. Okay you don't. Are you on the clan either?
You believe in it like you know, you know, you know, this you know the CK like the the the three
Straight out of K the KKK the CK
Answer see there's this finger. There's his fingers. What are you doing? Why are you making hands?
Why are you making masonic hand gestures at the at the watch?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I have to end the stream Chris. Oh my god
I don't want to I don't want to lose the stream because I'm white. Okay. Bye